<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Jobs generatedAt="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00" schemaVersion="1.0">
  <Job id="6903bb39-a203-470e-b517-62a621cee7c1" state="Michigan" district="Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools" districtId="Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Girls JV Soccer Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Girls JV Soccer Coach position at Grand Blanc High School is a key leadership role within the school's athletic program and wider learning community. This long-form description is designed to give prospective applicants a clear view of the expectations, responsibilities, and culture that surround the role. Coaches in this position are trusted to model character, support academic success, and help student‑athletes grow through meaningful experiences in practice, competition, and daily school life.

In this role, the Girls JV Soccer Coach works closely with the athletic director, school administrators, and other coaches to design and maintain a structured, developmentally appropriate program. That includes planning practices that blend fundamental skill instruction, competitive drills, and situational teaching so athletes understand both the technical and strategic sides of the game. The coach is responsible for teaching core skills, reinforcing proper technique, and helping athletes safely build strength, conditioning, and sport‑specific endurance.

The position also focuses heavily on culture and leadership. The Girls JV Soccer Coach at Grand Blanc High School sets the tone for effort, respect, and sportsmanship. This involves building clear expectations for behavior, guiding athletes through wins and losses with perspective, and maintaining standards that reflect the values of the school and community. Student‑athletes should come away from the program with improved confidence, stronger communication skills, and a better understanding of teamwork and accountability.

Another important part of the job is collaboration. The coach regularly communicates with teachers, counselors, and families to help student‑athletes balance athletics with academics and other responsibilities. At Grand Blanc High School, athletic participation is viewed as an extension of the classroom rather than a replacement for it. The Girls JV Soccer Coach encourages students to stay organized, meet eligibility requirements, and pursue long‑term goals in the classroom as well as on the field or court.

Program operations also fall under this role. The coach helps manage equipment, uniforms, and facilities, and assists with scheduling, transportation coordination, and adherence to league and district policies. The Girls JV Soccer Coach is expected to understand and follow all relevant regulations, including eligibility rules, sportsmanship guidelines, and safety standards, while maintaining current certifications such as CPR/First Aid as required by the district.

Finally, the Girls JV Soccer Coach position at Grand Blanc High School is a visible role that represents the school within the larger community. The coach interacts with families, officials, visiting teams, and youth programs, modeling professionalism in every setting. Candidates who are passionate about teaching, committed to student growth, and prepared to invest time and energy into the long‑term health of the program will find this role both challenging and rewarding.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Junior Varsity (JV) Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Girls Soccer</Sport>
    <Location>Grand Blanc High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>$2,601</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2024-12-09</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=32011</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=32011</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Grand Blanc High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Grand Blanc High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="12996ffa-f65c-4096-a6e9-16d0cefd9125" state="Michigan" district="Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools" districtId="Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Middle School Swim Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Middle School Swim Coach at Grand Blanc West Middle School is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Middle School Swim Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Grand Blanc West Middle School, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Middle School Swim Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Middle School Swim Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Middle School Swim Coach at Grand Blanc West Middle School allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Swim</Sport>
    <Location>Grand Blanc West Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>$2,468.00 per season</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-12-11</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-12-16</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=34005</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=34005</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Grand Blanc West Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Grand Blanc West Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="de7d3c6d-0e59-4e90-9641-d68af99a30e5" state="Missouri" district="Raytown C-II" districtId="Raytown C-II" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>High School Assistant Baseball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The High School Assistant Baseball Coach role at Raytown South High School is focused on helping student‑athletes unlock their potential through intentional coaching, structured practice environments, and a strong emphasis on character. This description outlines a position in which the coach is expected to be a planner, a teacher, a mentor, and a positive representative of the school community. Successful candidates bring energy to practices, patience to instruction, and clarity to expectations.

Practices form the backbone of the program, and the High School Assistant Baseball Coach is responsible for designing sessions that are purposeful and efficient. Each practice should have defined goals, from teaching new concepts to reinforcing previously learned skills or preparing for upcoming competition. The coach uses a variety of drills and teaching methods to keep athletes engaged, and regularly evaluates whether the team is progressing in the desired areas.

Coaches at Raytown South High School are also trusted to guide student‑athletes through challenges. That can include addressing frustrations after a tough loss, helping a student handle the pressure of increased responsibility, or supporting someone who is balancing school, family, and activities. The High School Assistant Baseball Coach listens, provides perspective, and reinforces the idea that effort, attitude, and resilience are as important as any statistical outcome.

Communication is a key strength of this position. The coach shares information about schedules, team policies, and expectations with families and staff in a timely and professional way. Within the team, the High School Assistant Baseball Coach encourages athletes to ask questions, give feedback, and support one another. This open communication helps prevent misunderstandings and builds trust.

Safety and compliance cannot be overlooked. The High School Assistant Baseball Coach follows all relevant policies regarding equipment, supervision, travel, and emergency procedures. The coach maintains current certifications as required and keeps up with best practices around conditioning, concussion awareness, and hydration. At Raytown South High School, the well‑being of student‑athletes is non‑negotiable.

This role is a good match for coaches who appreciate structure, care deeply about students, and are committed to building a consistent, values‑driven program. By serving as the High School Assistant Baseball Coach at Raytown South High School, a coach has the opportunity to make a lasting impact on young people while contributing to a respected and sustainable athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>Raytown South High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MO</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-06-09</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/raytownschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1619</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/raytownschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1619</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/raytownschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/raytownschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Raytown South High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Raytown C-II coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/raytownschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Raytown South High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="15c30ae6-af01-4ad2-a189-63ef76714cb5" state="North Carolina" district="Iredell-Statesville Schools" districtId="Iredell-Statesville Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Wrestling Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Wrestling Coach at West Iredell Middle School is a high‑engagement coaching role that calls for energy, clear communication, and a steady presence for student‑athletes. This position is built for a coach who enjoys being actively involved in every aspect of the program, from leading warm‑ups and teaching tactics to meeting with families and coordinating logistics. The coach is expected to bring consistency and enthusiasm to each interaction with the team.

Practices led by the Wrestling Coach are structured and purposeful. They begin with appropriate warm‑ups, transition into focused skill work, and conclude with competitive or situational activities that resemble live play. The coach introduces concepts in manageable steps and checks for understanding, encouraging athletes to ask questions and learn the reasoning behind drills and strategies. This approach helps athletes become smarter, more confident players.

Motivation is another key component of the job. Coaches at West Iredell Middle School use positive reinforcement, high yet realistic expectations, and clear feedback to help athletes push themselves. The Wrestling Coach recognizes effort and improvement, not just outcomes, and supports athletes through setbacks. This creates an environment where students are willing to take risks and grow.

The role also includes a strong communication element. The coach keeps families informed about schedules, travel, and program expectations, and responds to questions in a respectful, timely manner. Within the school, the Wrestling Coach collaborates with administrators and teachers to support students’ academic responsibilities, reinforcing that success in the classroom is essential.

Finally, the position requires adherence to safety and policy standards. The Wrestling Coach maintains appropriate supervision ratios, follows guidelines on equipment use, and ensures that emergency procedures are understood and practiced. The coach models appropriate conduct toward officials and opponents, reinforcing that competing with integrity is a core expectation at West Iredell Middle School. This comprehensive role is well suited to coaches who are organized, student‑focused, and eager to contribute to a strong athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>West Iredell Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2024-09-09</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5752</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5752</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>West Iredell Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Iredell-Statesville Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>West Iredell Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="fb9aa104-1ffa-4f13-b370-e5955333342e" state="North Carolina" district="Iredell-Statesville Schools" districtId="Iredell-Statesville Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Mens Tennis Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Mens Tennis Coach position at Statesville High School is an opportunity to shape a positive, inclusive, and hardworking team environment where students learn to love their sport and take pride in representing their school. This role emphasizes relationship‑building, clear expectations, and steady improvement over the course of a season and across multiple years of participation. The coach serves as a daily presence in the lives of student‑athletes, modeling the type of attitude and work ethic that leads to both athletic and personal growth.

At the core of the job is teaching. The Mens Tennis Coach is responsible for breaking down complex skills into manageable steps, offering demonstrations, and creating drills that allow athletes to practice safely and effectively. Practices should be organized around clear objectives, with time built in for warm‑up, instruction, repetition, and review. The coach gives frequent feedback, adjusts activities based on what athletes need, and encourages questions so that students remain engaged in their learning.

The role also involves nurturing team chemistry and a sense of belonging. At Statesville High School, coaches work to make sure every athlete feels included and respected. That means setting guidelines that prevent negative behavior, addressing conflicts quickly and fairly, and celebrating contributions from both starters and role players. The Mens Tennis Coach encourages athletes to support one another, communicate openly, and take pride in representing their school with class.

Beyond the field, court, track, or pool, the coach collaborates with school staff to support student‑athletes as whole people. That includes reinforcing academic expectations, respecting school policies, and helping students manage the demands of both athletics and coursework. Regular contact with families keeps everyone informed about schedules, expectations, and program goals, and offers a consistent channel for questions or concerns.

The Mens Tennis Coach also participates in broader program responsibilities such as attending department meetings, assisting with youth outreach or clinics, and contributing to long‑term planning. The coach is expected to stay current with best practices in training, injury prevention, and sport‑specific strategy, and to maintain any certifications required by the district or state association.

For individuals who enjoy working with young people, who believe in the value of school‑based athletics, and who are prepared to invest time in building a healthy team culture, the Mens Tennis Coach role at Statesville High School is a meaningful and impactful opportunity.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Mens Tennis</Sport>
    <Location>Statesville High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2024-10-21</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5815</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5815</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Statesville High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Iredell-Statesville Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Statesville High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="139ab551-1f47-466d-be0a-8404e88b671a" state="North Carolina" district="Iredell-Statesville Schools" districtId="Iredell-Statesville Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach role at West Iredell High School is focused on helping student‑athletes unlock their potential through intentional coaching, structured practice environments, and a strong emphasis on character. This description outlines a position in which the coach is expected to be a planner, a teacher, a mentor, and a positive representative of the school community. Successful candidates bring energy to practices, patience to instruction, and clarity to expectations.

Practices form the backbone of the program, and the Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach is responsible for designing sessions that are purposeful and efficient. Each practice should have defined goals, from teaching new concepts to reinforcing previously learned skills or preparing for upcoming competition. The coach uses a variety of drills and teaching methods to keep athletes engaged, and regularly evaluates whether the team is progressing in the desired areas.

Coaches at West Iredell High School are also trusted to guide student‑athletes through challenges. That can include addressing frustrations after a tough loss, helping a student handle the pressure of increased responsibility, or supporting someone who is balancing school, family, and activities. The Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach listens, provides perspective, and reinforces the idea that effort, attitude, and resilience are as important as any statistical outcome.

Communication is a key strength of this position. The coach shares information about schedules, team policies, and expectations with families and staff in a timely and professional way. Within the team, the Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach encourages athletes to ask questions, give feedback, and support one another. This open communication helps prevent misunderstandings and builds trust.

Safety and compliance cannot be overlooked. The Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach follows all relevant policies regarding equipment, supervision, travel, and emergency procedures. The coach maintains current certifications as required and keeps up with best practices around conditioning, concussion awareness, and hydration. At West Iredell High School, the well‑being of student‑athletes is non‑negotiable.

This role is a good match for coaches who appreciate structure, care deeply about students, and are committed to building a consistent, values‑driven program. By serving as the Mens/ Womens Tennis Coach at West Iredell High School, a coach has the opportunity to make a lasting impact on young people while contributing to a respected and sustainable athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Tennis</Sport>
    <Location>West Iredell High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-23</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=6015</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=6015</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>West Iredell High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Iredell-Statesville Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/issk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>West Iredell High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="d5c8ac35-d746-4baa-b2cd-0c8586d401a3" state="Nebraska" district="Gretna Public Sch." districtId="Gretna Public Sch." active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T07:24:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>COACH_Misc 2025/26 Coaching Opportunities</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The COACH_Misc 2025/26 Coaching Opportunities at Gretna Public Schools is an integral member of the school's educational team, using athletics as a platform for teaching discipline, teamwork, and perseverance. This position calls for a coach who is organized, reflective, and committed to continuous improvement, both for themselves and for their athletes. The role blends hands‑on coaching with program administration and relationship‑building.

From a coaching standpoint, the COACH_Misc 2025/26 Coaching Opportunities is responsible for teaching the rules, techniques, and strategies of the sport in a way that is accessible to student‑athletes. Practices are planned to include progressive skill work, position‑specific instruction, and opportunities for athletes to apply learning in controlled scrimmage situations. The coach pays attention to pacing and variety so that sessions remain engaging while still challenging students to stretch their comfort zones.

Culture is a central focus of this job. At Gretna Public Schools, the COACH_Misc 2025/26 Coaching Opportunities helps create a team environment where respect, honesty, and effort are expected. The coach sets clear standards regarding communication, attendance, and sportsmanship, and works with athletes to understand why these standards matter. When expectations are not met, the coach responds fairly, explaining consequences and encouraging athletes to learn from mistakes.

The position also requires responsiveness to student needs. Coaches remain aware of the emotional and academic pressures students face and adjust support accordingly. Checking in with athletes, acknowledging their efforts, and partnering with school staff all contribute to a positive experience. The COACH_Misc 2025/26 Coaching Opportunities may assist in connecting students with resources when additional support is needed.

Outside of direct coaching, the role involves tasks such as coordinating with officials and opponents, assisting with scheduling, and managing team communication channels. The coach must be punctual, prepared, and detail‑oriented, ensuring that events run smoothly and that the team represents Gretna Public Schools well at home and away.

Safety remains an ongoing responsibility. The COACH_Misc 2025/26 Coaching Opportunities follows district guidelines, maintains necessary certifications, and emphasizes proper warm‑up routines and technique to minimize risk of injury. This comprehensive approach to coaching allows student‑athletes to pursue their goals in a structured environment that prioritizes learning, well‑being, and long‑term success.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport/>
    <Location>District Wide - Gretna, Nebraska</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2024-02-19</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Posted until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://gpsne.schoolspring.com/?jobid=4977885</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://gpsne.schoolspring.com/?jobid=4977885</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://gpsne.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://gpsne.schoolspring.com/</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Gretna Public Schools</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Gretna Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://gpsne.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Gretna Public Sch.</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="71d531d0-817c-47c9-b7fb-9a245ed5ac71" state="North Carolina" district="Gaston County" districtId="Gaston County" active="false" lastSeen="2025-12-24T09:06:23+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High at South Point High is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At South Point High, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at South Point High operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent South Point High with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Assistant Coach - Wrestling @ South Point High role at South Point High.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>South Point High</Location>
    <City>Belmont</City>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://eobs.fa.us2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1001/jobs/preview/6214/?keyword=Coach&amp;mode=location</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://eobs.fa.us2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1001/jobs/preview/6214/?keyword=Coach&amp;mode=location</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://eobs.fa.us2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1001/jobs?keyword=Coach&amp;mode=location</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://eobs.fa.us2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1001/jobs?keyword=Coach&amp;mode=location</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>South Point High</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Gaston County coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://eobs.fa.us2.oraclecloud.com/hcmUI/CandidateExperience/en/sites/CX_1001/jobs?keyword=Coach&amp;mode=location</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>South Point High</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="ec29e0bc-0cc1-49df-abcb-cfd32dd59081" state="Maine" district="Sanford Public Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>JV Girls Lacrosse Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The JV Girls Lacrosse Coach role at Sanford High School is focused on building a competitive, well‑organized program that still prioritizes the overall well‑being of student‑athletes. This position blends strategy, culture‑building, and teaching, providing the coach with an opportunity to influence the direction of the program for years to come. The successful candidate will bring a clear vision for how to teach the sport, how to manage a team, and how to represent the school in a positive and professional manner.

From a competitive standpoint, the JV Girls Lacrosse Coach is responsible for developing seasonal plans that align practice content, conditioning work, and game preparation. This includes designing practice segments that progress from individual fundamentals to full‑team tactical execution. The coach should be comfortable breaking down film, identifying areas for improvement, and communicating game plans in a way that athletes can understand and apply under pressure.

Equally important is the culture created by the coach. At Sanford High School, teams are expected to demonstrate sportsmanship, respect, and unity. The JV Girls Lacrosse Coach sets standards for effort in practice, behavior in the classroom, and conduct in the community. That might involve establishing team guidelines, leading discussions about values, and recognizing athletes who demonstrate leadership or growth in those areas. The goal is to build a program where success is measured not just by wins and losses but by the quality of the experience for everyone involved.

This position also involves close coordination with the academic side of the school. The coach monitors eligibility, encourages students to keep up with assignments, and celebrates academic milestones. Communicating with teachers and counselors when necessary helps support student‑athletes as whole people, not just as performers in one activity. At Sanford High School, the JV Girls Lacrosse Coach is viewed as part of the educational team.

Program administration tasks include managing equipment and uniforms, tracking inventory, assisting with scheduling, and following all district and league regulations. The coach should be organized, punctual, and attentive to details such as transportation arrangements and roster paperwork. Safety protocols, including emergency action planning and injury‑reporting procedures, must be consistently followed.

Overall, the JV Girls Lacrosse Coach at Sanford High School is best suited for a coach who is excited about teaching, willing to collaborate with colleagues, and prepared to invest in the growth of student‑athletes over multiple seasons. It is an opportunity to provide structure, challenge, and support while representing the school with pride in the larger athletic community.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Junior Varsity (JV) Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Lacrosse</Sport>
    <Location>Sanford High School</Location>
    <City>Sanford</City>
    <State>ME</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-12-10</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2026-01-04</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/sanford/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=864</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/sanford/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=864</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/sanford/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=Coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/sanford/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=Coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Sanford High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Sanford Public Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/sanford/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=Coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Sanford High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="3420d69f-03a5-4334-b47e-ffb853d7c7f8" state="Michigan" district="L'Anse Creuse Public Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>JV Baseball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The JV Baseball Coach at L'Anse Creuse High School is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the JV Baseball Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At L'Anse Creuse High School, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The JV Baseball Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The JV Baseball Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the JV Baseball Coach at L'Anse Creuse High School allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Junior Varsity (JV) Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>L'Anse Creuse High School</Location>
    <City>Harrison Twp</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>48045</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>2026-01-05</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/lcps/opening/146233</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/lcps/opening/146233</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/lcps?search=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/lcps?search=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>L'Anse Creuse High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>L'Anse Creuse Public Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/lcps?search=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>L'Anse Creuse High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="c09ed382-b8a4-4520-b415-f7266d81ee54" state="Michigan" district="Waterford School District" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>JV Boys Baseball Coach - Kettering</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>Minimum Qualifications:
CPR/AED Certification required
First Aid Certification preferred
CAP Certification Preferred
Substantial knowledge of the fundamental and technical aspects of Baseball
Ability to effectively assist the varsity coach in building a Baseball program
Must abide by the Waterford School District Coaches Handbook and overall District athletic philosophy

Essential Functions:
Plan, organize and facilitate practices
Assist with oversight and management of games and practices
Assist baseball athletes in fundamental skills
Communicate effectively with all stakeholders
Work effectively with the entire coaching staff and athletic department
Teach, maintain and enforce character and academic expectations within the program

Reports To:
Varsity Boys Baseball Coach &amp; Building Assistant Athletic Director

Workday/Week:
Varies

Starting Date:
TBD

Compensation:
Determined by Teacher Master Agreement and years of experience

Posting Date:
July 10, 2025

Posting Deadline:
Until filled

Internal and external candidates may apply by visiting www.waterford.k12.mi.us and selecting the icon "Employment" and next, "Job Postings Directory". Include letter of intent, resume, and letter(s) of reference with the application. Employment is contingent upon receiving all required documentation (e.g., criminal background investigation and fingerprint records.)

The Board of Education does not discriminate...</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>Kettering High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-10</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=12692</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=12692</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=46173&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=46173&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Kettering High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Waterford School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=46173&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Kettering High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="acd2f4a5-edfb-42e6-91c6-232f4f411440" state="Michigan" district="Waterford School District" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Freshman (JVB) Boys Baseball Coach - Kettering</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>Minimum Qualifications:
CPR/AED Certification required
First Aid Certification preferred
CAP Certification Preferred
Substantial knowledge of the fundamental and technical aspects of Baseball
Ability to effectively assist the varsity coach in building a Baseball program
Must abide by the Waterford School District Coaches Handbook and overall District athletic philosophy

Essential Functions:
Plan, organize and facilitate practices
Assist with oversight and management of games and practices
Assist baseball athletes in fundamental skills
Communicate effectively with all stakeholders
Work effectively with the entire coaching staff and athletic department
Teach, maintain and enforce character and academic expectations within the program

Reports To:
Varsity Boys Baseball Coach &amp; Building Assistant Athletic Director

Workday/Week:
Varies

Starting Date:
TBD

Compensation:
Determined by Teacher Master Agreement and years of experience

Posting Date:
July 10, 2025

Posting Deadline:
Until filled

Internal and external candidates may apply by visiting www.waterford.k12.mi.us and selecting the icon "Employment" and next, "Job Postings Directory". Include letter of intent, resume, and letter(s) of reference with the application. Employment is contingent upon receiving all required documentation (e.g., criminal background investigation and fingerprint records.)

The Board of Education does not discriminate...</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>Kettering High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-10</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=12691</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=12691</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=46173&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=46173&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Kettering High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Waterford School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/OAKLANDSCHOOLS/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=46173&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Kettering High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="64dc460b-e74d-4d66-b91e-5ca3ba8b6ae5" state="Nebraska" district="Omaha Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Coach, Middle School 2025-2026 School Year</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>POSITION TITLE: Assistant Coach, Middle School

QUALIFICATIONS
Prior coaching experience required.

RESPONSIBILITIES
The assistant coach for any sport has the responsibility for supporting the athletics program in a manner that serves the best interests of the school district and of the student athletes who participate in that program. The assistant coach supports and works cooperatively with the varsity head coach, performing all assigned duties and providing support and assistance as requested. The assistant coach ensures that actions and activities are consistent with and supportive of the athletics program as well as the rules identified by the Nebraska School Activities Association. The assistant coach adheres at all times to the Policies and Regulations and the Practices and Procedures of the Board of Education.

Specific Duties and Responsibilities
1. Ensures the safety and well-being of all student participants.
2. Attends practices and competitive events consistently, demonstrating punctual arrival.
3. Supports and applies approved expectations for learning and classroom performance as a condition for participation in athletics. Monitors and supports students' academic performance to ensure success.
4. Sets and maintains high expectations for the conduct of student athletes, supervising students to assure that all conduct presents the school and the school district in a positive manner.
5. Supports and applies the head coach's plan for teaching and encouraging appropriate student behavior including possible consequences for unacceptable behavior. Assures that the plan is used to support the development of the student athletes and to promote the success of the athletics program.
6. Supports and teaches the athletics program designed by the head coach, enhancing the development of skills and encouraging team play during instruction, practice, and competitive events.
7. Gathers accurate information regarding eligibility of student athletes and provides it to the head coach in a timely manner. Supports the letter and the spirit of eligibility criteria as determined by the school and the district, as well as local and state governing bodies.
8. Participates in district-approved activities with elementary students at the request of the head coach.
9. Communicates effectively with students, staff, and parents.
10. Communicates with the head coach regarding important changes, problems or developments potentially affecting the athletics program or the school.
11. Works cooperatively with all coaches and officials to provide the best possible experience for student-athletes and fans.
12. Supports and contributes to the success of the entire athletics program by encouraging student participation and support for all programs and assisting other programs whenever possible.
13. Communicates with building administrators regarding important changes, problems or developments potentially affecting the athletics program or the school.
14. Supports and contributes to the success of the entire athletics program and the school by encouraging student participation and support for all programs and assisting other programs and coaches whenever possible.

Coaching
1. Plans and schedules all activities related to the athletics program in conjunction with the Head Coach and Athletic Director and in conformance with rules of local and state governing bodies.
2. May design and implement strength and conditioning program that supports the health and safety of student-athletes and promotes the success of the program.
3. Designs practice activities that enhance the development of athletics skills, deepen student-athletes' understanding of the sport, and emphasize the importance of team play to the success of the program. Practices are ordered, with purposeful activities designed to elicit high levels of participation and to emphasize elements of individual and team excellence.
4. Leads student athletes and staff in preparing for and participating in competitive events. Manages all resources effectively to enhance growth, to maximize opportunities for success, and to present the program and the school in a positive manner.
5. Assures that all student participants have arrangements for safe return to the care of respective parent(s) or guardian(s) at the conclusion of activities daily.

Program Administration
1. Oversees the safety conditions of the facility and reports concerns immediately to the appropriate authority.
2. Establishes and maintains an inventory of equipment used in the athletics program and is accountable for the condition and return of all equipment. Monitors program needs and recommends replacement of equipment, supplies, and uniforms in advance of need when possible.
3. Obtains required documentation regarding student eligibility for participation in interscholastic athletics.
4. Assures that reliable data regarding individual and team performances are maintained and reported in a timely manner.
5. Maintains records regarding financial expenditures and reimbursements and submits required reports in a timely manner.
6. Submits an end-of-season report reporting required data and evaluating the success of the program including recommendations for its improvement

* NOTE: The statements herein are intended to describe the general nature and level of work being performed by people assigned to this classification. They are not intended to be construed, as an exhaustive list of all responsibilities, duties, and skills required of personnel so classified.
EQUAL OPPORTUNITY EMPLOYER</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Strength and Conditioning</JobType>
    <Sport>Weightlifting</Sport>
    <Location>Omaha, NE</Location>
    <City>Omaha</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>68131</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-05-06</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2026-05-01</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5146857</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5146857</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>careers@ops.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Omaha Public Schools</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Omaha Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Omaha Public Sch.</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="1cc34f8f-6c00-47e3-8504-b7eb2b07276e" state="Nebraska" district="Omaha Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Coach, High School for 2025-2026 School Year</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Assistant Coach, High School for 2025-2026 School Year position at Omaha Public Schools provides an opportunity to guide student‑athletes through an experience that combines challenge, support, and growth. This role is intended for coaches who see beyond wins and losses and who value the lasting impact that a positive athletic program can have on young people. Through careful planning, consistent expectations, and ongoing communication, the coach helps create a framework where athletes can thrive.

From an instructional perspective, the Assistant Coach, High School for 2025-2026 School Year prepares practices that sequence learning effectively. Early sessions may focus heavily on fundamentals and basic systems, while later practices refine execution and introduce more advanced concepts. The coach uses demonstrations, targeted drills, and guided scrimmages to help athletes apply what they learn. Regular assessment allows the coach to adjust plans based on the team’s progress.

The position also requires deliberate attention to team culture. At Omaha Public Schools, the Assistant Coach, High School for 2025-2026 School Year works to ensure that the environment is welcoming, fair, and focused on collective responsibility. The coach sets expectations around effort, communication, and respect, and follows through when those expectations are not met. Celebrating positive examples and giving athletes leadership opportunities strengthens the sense of ownership within the group.

Support for the broader student experience is built into the job. Coaches stay informed about academic calendars, test periods, and other school events so that practices and competitions are scheduled thoughtfully whenever possible. The Assistant Coach, High School for 2025-2026 School Year encourages athletes to communicate about conflicts in advance and to take initiative in managing their commitments. When students feel supported in both academics and athletics, they are more likely to remain engaged and successful.

Administrative responsibilities include coordination with the athletic department, assisting with transportation, submitting required paperwork, and maintaining accurate rosters. The coach must be attentive to detail and willing to complete these tasks reliably, as they directly affect the experience of athletes and families.

At its core, the Assistant Coach, High School for 2025-2026 School Year at Omaha Public Schools is a chance to teach, to mentor, and to build something that extends beyond a single season. Candidates who are motivated by the opportunity to help students grow through sport will find this position especially meaningful.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Specialty Sports</Sport>
    <Location>Omaha, Nebraska 68131</Location>
    <City>Omaha</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>68131</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-05-06</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2026-05-01</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5146864</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5146864</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>careers@ops.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Omaha Public Schools</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Omaha Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://omaha.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Omaha Public Sch.</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="ed0a50d3-03a3-4506-b2f2-4dc23e635f7a" state="Nebraska" district="Lincoln Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Coaches/Event Workers, Middle School Athletics, 2025-2026</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Coaches/Event Workers, Middle School Athletics, 2025 at Lincoln Public Schools is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Coaches/Event Workers, Middle School Athletics, 2025 manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Lincoln Public Schools, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Coaches/Event Workers, Middle School Athletics, 2025 demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Coaches/Event Workers, Middle School Athletics, 2025 follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Coaches/Event Workers, Middle School Athletics, 2025 at Lincoln Public Schools allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Specialty Sports</Sport>
    <Location>Lincoln, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Lincoln</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>$13.50 to $18.50 Per Hour</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-06-02</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2026-05-11</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://lincoln.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5167738</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://lincoln.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5167738</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://lincoln.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>hr@lps.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Lincoln Public Schools</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Lincoln Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://lincoln.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Lincoln Public Sch.</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="8c46bc7f-f9cb-482e-9ddb-4e18761fa50a" state="Nebraska" district="Fremont Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School at Fremont Public Schools is an integral member of the school's educational team, using athletics as a platform for teaching discipline, teamwork, and perseverance. This position calls for a coach who is organized, reflective, and committed to continuous improvement, both for themselves and for their athletes. The role blends hands‑on coaching with program administration and relationship‑building.

From a coaching standpoint, the Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School is responsible for teaching the rules, techniques, and strategies of the sport in a way that is accessible to student‑athletes. Practices are planned to include progressive skill work, position‑specific instruction, and opportunities for athletes to apply learning in controlled scrimmage situations. The coach pays attention to pacing and variety so that sessions remain engaging while still challenging students to stretch their comfort zones.

Culture is a central focus of this job. At Fremont Public Schools, the Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School helps create a team environment where respect, honesty, and effort are expected. The coach sets clear standards regarding communication, attendance, and sportsmanship, and works with athletes to understand why these standards matter. When expectations are not met, the coach responds fairly, explaining consequences and encouraging athletes to learn from mistakes.

The position also requires responsiveness to student needs. Coaches remain aware of the emotional and academic pressures students face and adjust support accordingly. Checking in with athletes, acknowledging their efforts, and partnering with school staff all contribute to a positive experience. The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School may assist in connecting students with resources when additional support is needed.

Outside of direct coaching, the role involves tasks such as coordinating with officials and opponents, assisting with scheduling, and managing team communication channels. The coach must be punctual, prepared, and detail‑oriented, ensuring that events run smoothly and that the team represents Fremont Public Schools well at home and away.

Safety remains an ongoing responsibility. The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School follows district guidelines, maintains necessary certifications, and emphasizes proper warm‑up routines and technique to minimize risk of injury. This comprehensive approach to coaching allows student‑athletes to pursue their goals in a structured environment that prioritizes learning, well‑being, and long‑term success.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
    <Location>Middle School - Fremont, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Fremont</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>As Per Extra Duty Schedule</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-01</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Open Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5265563</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5265563</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>hr@fpsmail.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Fremont Public Schools</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Fremont Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Fremont Public Sch.</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="5e2bbbb2-6386-4faf-b422-d9168918d1a8" state="North Carolina" district="Buncombe County" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:32:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>P.E. / Health Teacher (Assistant Football Coach AND either Wrestling / Baseball Coach)</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>Position Purpose: Under the general supervision of the School Principal, to develop students' physical skills and abilities, strength, agility, poise, coordination, and teamwork; to develop students' understanding of the importance of exercise to physical and mental well-being; and to motivate students to work towards, physical fitness, hygiene, and good health. Click to view the Teacher job description.

Additionally, this position will be required to serve in an assistant football coaching role AND either a wrestling or baseball coach. This will be a permanent expectation of this position. For specific coaching details, please email our A.C. Reynolds Athletic Director, Coach Steve McCurry (charles.mccurry@bcsemail.org). With all coaching positions, there is a supplemental pay based on years experience.

Minimum Degree Level: Bachelor's Degree (click here for more info about Master's pay) Alternative Licensed Pathways: If you are offered a position with BCS, our licensure specialist can share information on the 1-year Emergency License and later work with you to convert this to a Residency License. Qualifications:
Bachelor's degree
18 semester hours of relevant coursework
2.7 GPA (undergraduate coursework or post-graduate coursework)
Ability to produce an official, degree dated transcript from an accredited university
Former Lateral Entry license candidates are eligible to apply
Email our licensure specialist, shonda.haynes@bcsemail.org, if you have licensure questions. Email the School or Department for specific job questions.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Licensed- General/P.E. / Health Teacher</JobType>
    <Sport>Football, Baseball, Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>AC Reynolds High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>State Teacher Salary + [10.5% - 18% local supplement]</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-12-19</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2026-01-04</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/buncombeschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=14729</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/buncombeschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=14729</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/buncombeschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>charles.mccurry@bcsemail.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>AC Reynolds High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Buncombe County coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/buncombeschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>AC Reynolds High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="b5c3a001-7481-4e8d-8656-bf686e93999f" state="Maine" district="Regional School Unit 6" districtId="Regional School Unit 6" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:37:37+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Football Coach, 7th Grade</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Football Coach, 7th Grade role at Bonny Eagle Middle School emphasizes collaboration, consistency, and long‑term program development. This position is ideal for a coach who enjoys working as part of a broader athletic staff and who values building connections across grade levels and teams. The goal is to help create a smooth pathway for student‑athletes as they progress, while maintaining a recognizable identity and standard of excellence for the program.

In practical terms, the Football Coach, 7th Grade coordinates closely with the athletic director and fellow coaches to align terminology, teaching priorities, and expectations. This might involve participating in coaching meetings, sharing practice plans, and adapting approaches so that athletes experience similar structures and messages at each level. At Bonny Eagle Middle School, the program is strongest when coaches communicate and support one another.

Day‑to‑day responsibilities include designing practices that teach core skills, reinforcing team concepts, and preparing athletes for competition. The coach works to balance repetition with variety, ensuring that key fundamentals are constantly reinforced while athletes also experience new challenges. The Football Coach, 7th Grade reviews performance with the team, helping athletes learn how to analyze both successes and mistakes in a constructive way.

The role extends into community and family engagement. Coaches represent Bonny Eagle Middle School at games, parent meetings, and potential youth outreach events. The Football Coach, 7th Grade may help host clinics or camps, encourage younger students to try the sport, and provide information about expectations to families who are new to the program. A welcoming, organized presence can greatly influence how the program is perceived.

Athlete support is ongoing. The Football Coach, 7th Grade monitors team morale, assists students in managing the demands of school and sport, and reinforces the importance of rest, nutrition, and healthy habits. The coach keeps the focus on sustainable growth rather than shortcuts, emphasizing that consistent effort over time leads to meaningful improvement.

Administrative tasks such as roster management, schedule communication, and equipment oversight are also part of the position. The Football Coach, 7th Grade must handle these responsibilities reliably, as they are essential to maintaining a well‑run program. Coaches who enjoy seeing the big picture, who are willing to share ideas, and who care about the experience of every athlete will thrive in this role at Bonny Eagle Middle School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
    <Location>Bonny Eagle Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>ME</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-12-08</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5462139</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5462139</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://bonnyeagle.org/en-US/employment-7d0a522b</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://bonnyeagle.org/en-US/employment-7d0a522b</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Bonny Eagle Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Regional School Unit 6 coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://bonnyeagle.org/en-US/employment-7d0a522b</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Bonny Eagle Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="2bc18707-9647-4313-bd5b-b829db184d92" state="Michigan" district="Plymouth-Canton Community Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T07:54:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Boys Lacrosse - JV Head Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Boys Lacrosse - JV Head Coach at SALEM HIGH SCHOOL is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Boys Lacrosse - JV Head Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At SALEM HIGH SCHOOL, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Boys Lacrosse - JV Head Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Boys Lacrosse - JV Head Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Boys Lacrosse - JV Head Coach at SALEM HIGH SCHOOL allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head JV Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Lacrosse</Sport>
    <Location>SALEM HIGH SCHOOL</Location>
    <City>Canton</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>According to the Master Agreement - Schedule "B"</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-11-06</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1425</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1425</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>chechaka.johnson@pccsk12.com</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>SALEM HIGH SCHOOL</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Plymouth-Canton Community Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>SALEM HIGH SCHOOL</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="11bfce27-c41f-49e7-a95c-63b71fbb6348" state="Michigan" district="Troy School District" districtId="Troy School District" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:05:53+00:00">
    <JobTitle>8th Grade Girls Volleyball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The 8th Grade Girls Volleyball Coach at Larson Middle School is an integral member of the school's educational team, using athletics as a platform for teaching discipline, teamwork, and perseverance. This position calls for a coach who is organized, reflective, and committed to continuous improvement, both for themselves and for their athletes. The role blends hands‑on coaching with program administration and relationship‑building.

From a coaching standpoint, the 8th Grade Girls Volleyball Coach is responsible for teaching the rules, techniques, and strategies of the sport in a way that is accessible to student‑athletes. Practices are planned to include progressive skill work, position‑specific instruction, and opportunities for athletes to apply learning in controlled scrimmage situations. The coach pays attention to pacing and variety so that sessions remain engaging while still challenging students to stretch their comfort zones.

Culture is a central focus of this job. At Larson Middle School, the 8th Grade Girls Volleyball Coach helps create a team environment where respect, honesty, and effort are expected. The coach sets clear standards regarding communication, attendance, and sportsmanship, and works with athletes to understand why these standards matter. When expectations are not met, the coach responds fairly, explaining consequences and encouraging athletes to learn from mistakes.

The position also requires responsiveness to student needs. Coaches remain aware of the emotional and academic pressures students face and adjust support accordingly. Checking in with athletes, acknowledging their efforts, and partnering with school staff all contribute to a positive experience. The 8th Grade Girls Volleyball Coach may assist in connecting students with resources when additional support is needed.

Outside of direct coaching, the role involves tasks such as coordinating with officials and opponents, assisting with scheduling, and managing team communication channels. The coach must be punctual, prepared, and detail‑oriented, ensuring that events run smoothly and that the team represents Larson Middle School well at home and away.

Safety remains an ongoing responsibility. The 8th Grade Girls Volleyball Coach follows district guidelines, maintains necessary certifications, and emphasizes proper warm‑up routines and technique to minimize risk of injury. This comprehensive approach to coaching allows student‑athletes to pursue their goals in a structured environment that prioritizes learning, well‑being, and long‑term success.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Girls Volleyball</Sport>
    <Location>Larson Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-09-23</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/troy/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1775</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/troy/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1775</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/troy/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/troy/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Larson Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Troy School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/troy/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Larson Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="7c2e0c4f-0e1d-4e54-853c-139d89a01fb0" state="Michigan" district="Huron Valley Schools" districtId="Huron Valley Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:15:30+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School at Lakeland High School is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At Lakeland High School, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at Lakeland High School operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent Lakeland High School with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Head Football Coach-Lakeland High School role at Lakeland High School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
    <Location>Lakeland High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=14749</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=14749</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Lakeland High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Huron Valley Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Lakeland High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="f5277c0d-d693-4107-bb73-b70ad4e32bcc" state="Michigan" district="Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:25:18+00:00">
    <JobTitle>9th Grade Girls Basketball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>2025-2026 School Year
If you are recommended for the position and are not currently a GBCS employee, your employer will be GECS.
Experience as a coach or participant preferred.
Nondiscrimination: The Grand Blanc Board of Education is committed to a policy of non-discrimination in relation to race, color, gender, religion, height, weight, marital status, disability, or national origin. The board-appointed coordinator for all concerns and complaints for issues relating to Title IX, Section 504, the Age Discrimination Act and Title II is:
Deputy Superintendent or Director of Personnel
Administration Building • 11920 S. Saginaw • Grand Blanc, MI 48439
(810) 591-6001 • www.gbcs.org</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Athletics/Activities/Coaching</JobType>
    <Sport>Basketball</Sport>
    <Location>Grand Blanc High School</Location>
    <City>Grand Blanc</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>48439</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>$3,057.00 per Season</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-12-05</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=33972</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=33972</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Grand Blanc High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Grand Blanc High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="49df8e45-3de2-496d-a786-5095ee592b92" state="Michigan" district="Plymouth-Canton Community Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:37:31+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Boys Baseball - Assistant Freshman Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:
1. High school graduate or equivalent
2. Applicants must have experience in high school level coaching or playing at college or university level in sport to which they are applying.
3. Applicant must have a time schedule compatible with that of the high school.
4. CPR and/or first aide training preferred.
5. Demonstrated ability to work with parents and children.
REPORTS TO: Assistant Principal of Activities and Athletics
RATE OF PAY: According to the Master Agreement - Schedule "B"
BEGINNING DATE: Spring 2024/25
DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:
1. The coach will be responsible for the entire organization of the sport to which he/she is assigned.
2. The coach will be directly responsible for all equipment in his/her sport. A complete inventory of all equipment will be filed with the director at the end of each season.
3. The coach will be responsible for all awards presented in his/her sport and a season summary.
4. Bending, lifting, and overhead work required.
5. Performs other tasks as assigned.
This description is intended to describe the essential job functions, the general supplemental functions and the essential requirements for the performance of this job. It is not an exhaustive list of all duties, responsibilities and requirements of a person so classified. Other functions may be assigned and management retains the right to add or change the duties at any time.
EVALUATION: Performance of this position will be evaluated annually.
METHOD OF APPLICATION: Internal and external applicants should email a completed coaching application and cover letter to Chechaka Johnson, Chechaka.johnson@pccsk12.com
To see the posting, click here
External applicants will be hired and paid by Edustaff.
DEADLINE FOR APPLICATION: Open until filled</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL</Location>
    <City>Canton</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>48187</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2024-11-26</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1131</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1131</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>Chechaka.johnson@pccsk12.com</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Plymouth High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Plymouth-Canton Community Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Plymouth High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="428c16c5-71cc-42bc-ab16-82eb96103089" state="Michigan" district="Huron Valley Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:37:31+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Coach Boys Varsity Cross Country LHS</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>POSITION DESCRIPTION

Huron Valley Schools is seeking an enthusiastic, energetic, and innovative Assistant Coach for Boys Varsity Cross Country

Position Type: Athletics/Activities/Coaching
Location: Lakeland High School
Salary: Per contract Schedule B
Reports To: Athletic Director
Status: School Year 2024 - 2025
Start Date: ASAP

MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS
    Able to instruct athletes in the fundamental skills, strategy, and physical training necessary for athletes to realize a degree of individual and team success
    Coaching experience preferred
    Playing experience at the high school or college level is preferred

ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS
    Provide proper safeguards for maintenance and protection of assigned equipment sites
    Perform other duties which may be assigned bv
 the Athletic Director
    Instills in each player a respect for equipment, and school property
    The position includes other unusual aspects such as extended time, risk injury factors and due process predicaments
    Implement and design clinics in order to promote the sport
    Schedule all practices, clinics, camps and competitions
    Continue to grow professionally bv attending seminars and clinics
    Maintains discipline and works to increase morale and cooperation

EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE: High School diploma and/or related experience.
LANGUAGE, MATHEMATICAL AND REASONING SKILLS: Ability to speak and write effectively. Ability to apply mathematical concepts to practical situations. Ability to carry out instructions furnished in written or oral format and deal with problems involving several concrete variables in standardized situations.

PHYSICAL DEMANDS: The physical demands described here are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.

While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to sit, talk, or hear. The employee is occasionally required to stand, walk and reach with hands or arms. Specific vision abilities required by this job include close vision and ability to adjust and focus.

WORK ENVIRONMENT: The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.

METHOD OF APPLICATION
A cover letter is required in order to be considered for this position and should be attached as the first page of your resume. The cover letter should outline skills and experience that directly relate to the qualifications for the position.

Please send letter of intent and coaching resume to:

Todd Miller
Lakeland HS Athletic Director
todd.miller@hvs.org

Inquiries should be addressed to:
Jeanna Klebba
Human Resources Administrative Assistant
2390 South Milford Rd., Highland, MI 48357
248.684.8217 (TELEPHONE) • 248.684.8266 (FAX)
E-MAIL: jeanna.klebba@hvs.org</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Cross Country</Sport>
    <Location>Lakeland High School</Location>
    <City>Highland</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>48357</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Per contract Schedule B</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-04</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=11130</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=11130</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>todd.miller@hvs.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Lakeland High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Huron Valley Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Lakeland High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="e6e6e771-d0b2-4768-899f-00720998abea" state="Michigan" district="Huron Valley Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:37:31+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Girls Swim Coach Milford High School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>POSITION DESCRIPTION

Huron Valley Schools is seeking an enthusiastic, energetic, and innovative Assistant Girls Swim Coach.

Position Type: Athletics/Activities/Coaching
Location: Milford High School
Salary: Per contract Schedule B
Reports To: Athletic Director
Status: School Year 2025 - 2026
Start Date: ASAP

MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS
    Able to instruct athletes in the fundamental skills, strategy, and physical training necessary for athletes to realize a degree of individual and team success
    Coaching experience preferred
    Playing experience at the high school or college level is preferred

ESSENTIAL FUNCTIONS
    Provide proper safeguards for maintenance and protection of assigned equipment sites
    Perform other duties which may be assigned by the Athletic Director
    Instills in each player a respect for equipment, and school property
    The position includes other unusual aspects such as extended time, risk injury factors and due process predicaments
    Implement and design clinics in order to promote the sport
    Schedule all practices, clinics, camps and competitions
    Continue to grow professionally by attending seminars and clinics
    Maintains discipline and works to increase morale and cooperation

EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE: High School diploma and/or related experience.
LANGUAGE, MATHEMATICAL AND REASONING SKILLS: Ability to speak and write effectively. Ability to apply mathematical concepts to practical situations. Ability to carry out instructions furnished in written or oral format and deal with problems involving several concrete variables in standardized situations.

PHYSICAL DEMANDS: The physical demands described here are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.

While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to sit, talk, or hear. The employee is occasionally required to stand, walk and reach with hands or arms. Specific vision abilities required by this job include close vision and ability to adjust and focus.

WORK ENVIRONMENT: The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.

METHOD OF APPLICATION
A cover letter is required in order to be considered for this position and should be attached as the first page of your resume. The cover letter should outline skills and experience that directly relate to the qualifications for the position.

Please send letter of intent and coaching resume to:

Jim Marszalek
Milford HS Athletic Director
jim.marszalek@hvs.org

Inquiries should be addressed to:
Jeanna Klebba
Human Resources Administrative Assistant
2390 South Milford Rd., Highland, MI 48357
248.684.8217 (TELEPHONE) • 248.684.8266 (FAX)
E-MAIL: jeanna.klebba@hvs.org</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Swimming and Diving</Sport>
    <Location>Milford High School</Location>
    <City>Highland</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>48357</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Per contract Schedule B</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-06-25</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=12529</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=12529</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>jim.marszalek@hvs.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Milford High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Huron Valley Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/oaklandschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?%20district=994911&amp;choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=46164&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Milford High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="9bbb0cc3-e73f-458a-be0d-dfc82645be22" state="Michigan" district="Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:37:31+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Girls JV Soccer Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Girls JV Soccer Coach role at Grand Blanc High School is focused on building a competitive, well‑organized program that still prioritizes the overall well‑being of student‑athletes. This position blends strategy, culture‑building, and teaching, providing the coach with an opportunity to influence the direction of the program for years to come. The successful candidate will bring a clear vision for how to teach the sport, how to manage a team, and how to represent the school in a positive and professional manner.

From a competitive standpoint, the Girls JV Soccer Coach is responsible for developing seasonal plans that align practice content, conditioning work, and game preparation. This includes designing practice segments that progress from individual fundamentals to full‑team tactical execution. The coach should be comfortable breaking down film, identifying areas for improvement, and communicating game plans in a way that athletes can understand and apply under pressure.

Equally important is the culture created by the coach. At Grand Blanc High School, teams are expected to demonstrate sportsmanship, respect, and unity. The Girls JV Soccer Coach sets standards for effort in practice, behavior in the classroom, and conduct in the community. That might involve establishing team guidelines, leading discussions about values, and recognizing athletes who demonstrate leadership or growth in those areas. The goal is to build a program where success is measured not just by wins and losses but by the quality of the experience for everyone involved.

This position also involves close coordination with the academic side of the school. The coach monitors eligibility, encourages students to keep up with assignments, and celebrates academic milestones. Communicating with teachers and counselors when necessary helps support student‑athletes as whole people, not just as performers in one activity. At Grand Blanc High School, the Girls JV Soccer Coach is viewed as part of the educational team.

Program administration tasks include managing equipment and uniforms, tracking inventory, assisting with scheduling, and following all district and league regulations. The coach should be organized, punctual, and attentive to details such as transportation arrangements and roster paperwork. Safety protocols, including emergency action planning and injury‑reporting procedures, must be consistently followed.

Overall, the Girls JV Soccer Coach at Grand Blanc High School is best suited for a coach who is excited about teaching, willing to collaborate with colleagues, and prepared to invest in the growth of student‑athletes over multiple seasons. It is an opportunity to provide structure, challenge, and support while representing the school with pride in the larger athletic community.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Athletics/Activities/Coaching</JobType>
    <Sport>Soccer</Sport>
    <Location>Grand Blanc High School</Location>
    <City>Grand Blanc</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience>Experience as a coach or participant preferred.</Experience>
    <SalaryRange>$2,601</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2024-12-09</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=32011</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=32011</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Grand Blanc High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Grand Blanc Commmunity Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/gcaps/onlineapp/default.aspx?choosedistrict=true&amp;applitrackclient=729&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Grand Blanc High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="4434fd8a-df72-40d2-8691-6145cbaadb1f" state="Missouri" district="Francis Howell" districtId="Francis Howell" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:40:29+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach role at Francis Howell Central High School emphasizes collaboration, consistency, and long‑term program development. This position is ideal for a coach who enjoys working as part of a broader athletic staff and who values building connections across grade levels and teams. The goal is to help create a smooth pathway for student‑athletes as they progress, while maintaining a recognizable identity and standard of excellence for the program.

In practical terms, the Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach coordinates closely with the athletic director and fellow coaches to align terminology, teaching priorities, and expectations. This might involve participating in coaching meetings, sharing practice plans, and adapting approaches so that athletes experience similar structures and messages at each level. At Francis Howell Central High School, the program is strongest when coaches communicate and support one another.

Day‑to‑day responsibilities include designing practices that teach core skills, reinforcing team concepts, and preparing athletes for competition. The coach works to balance repetition with variety, ensuring that key fundamentals are constantly reinforced while athletes also experience new challenges. The Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach reviews performance with the team, helping athletes learn how to analyze both successes and mistakes in a constructive way.

The role extends into community and family engagement. Coaches represent Francis Howell Central High School at games, parent meetings, and potential youth outreach events. The Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach may help host clinics or camps, encourage younger students to try the sport, and provide information about expectations to families who are new to the program. A welcoming, organized presence can greatly influence how the program is perceived.

Athlete support is ongoing. The Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach monitors team morale, assists students in managing the demands of school and sport, and reinforces the importance of rest, nutrition, and healthy habits. The coach keeps the focus on sustainable growth rather than shortcuts, emphasizing that consistent effort over time leads to meaningful improvement.

Administrative tasks such as roster management, schedule communication, and equipment oversight are also part of the position. The Baseball Coach ~ JV Head Coach must handle these responsibilities reliably, as they are essential to maintaining a well‑run program. Coaches who enjoy seeing the big picture, who are willing to share ideas, and who care about the experience of every athlete will thrive in this role at Francis Howell Central High School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head JV Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>Francis Howell Central High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MO</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/fhsd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=9654</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/fhsd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=9654</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/fhsd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/fhsd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Francis Howell Central High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Francis Howell coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/fhsd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Francis Howell Central High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="ea7927e3-c6f6-4684-b819-4a86e29dc8b0" state="Missouri" district="Independence" districtId="Independence" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T08:48:58+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head Girls Wrestling Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head Girls Wrestling Coach at William Chrisman High School is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Head Girls Wrestling Coach is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At William Chrisman High School, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Head Girls Wrestling Coach helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Head Girls Wrestling Coach works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at William Chrisman High School operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent William Chrisman High School with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Head Girls Wrestling Coach reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Head Girls Wrestling Coach role at William Chrisman High School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>William Chrisman High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MO</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/isdschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=4016</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/isdschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=4016</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/isdschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/isdschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>William Chrisman High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Independence coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/isdschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>William Chrisman High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="07edc0cd-4cf2-43a7-84bc-69a94dbe3839" state="Montana" district="Helena Public Schools" districtId="Helena Public Schools" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T09:07:01+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Swim Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Assistant Swim Coach at Capital and Helena High School is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Assistant Swim Coach is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At Capital and Helena High School, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Assistant Swim Coach helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Assistant Swim Coach works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at Capital and Helena High School operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent Capital and Helena High School with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Assistant Swim Coach reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Assistant Swim Coach role at Capital and Helena High School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Swim</Sport>
    <Location>All High Schools</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>MT</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/helena/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=3126</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/helena/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=3126</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/helena/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=Coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/helena/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=Coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Capital and Helena High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Helena Public Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/helena/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=Coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Capital and Helena High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="46651c99-50c0-419e-a84c-fa38ffb2bbb7" state="North Carolina" district="Union County Public Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T09:21:07+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Girls Wrestling Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Girls Wrestling Coach at Union County Public Schools is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Girls Wrestling Coach is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At Union County Public Schools, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Girls Wrestling Coach helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Girls Wrestling Coach works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at Union County Public Schools operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent Union County Public Schools with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Girls Wrestling Coach reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Girls Wrestling Coach role at Union County Public Schools.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>Monroe Middle</Location>
    <City>Monroe</City>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-08-06</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=15048</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=15048</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Union County Public Schools</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Union County Public Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Union County Public Schools</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="be62853d-d76b-438f-8f98-efed8c5e79a5" state="North Carolina" district="Union County Public Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T09:56:41+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Middle School Softball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>Position Type:
  Athletics- High School/ Middle School Coaches

Date Posted:
  6/24/2025

Location:
  Porter Ridge Middle

Overview:
As a Middle School Softball Coach, you will be responsible for coaching and leading the school's softball team. You will work with students to enhance their softball skills, promote teamwork, and instill a love for the sport.

Responsibilities:
Organize and conduct regular practices to improve players' skills in batting, pitching, fielding, and base running.
Develop game strategies and tactics to maximize the team's performance.
Provide guidance and mentorship to student-athletes, both on and off the field.
Foster a supportive and respectful team environment that encourages sportsmanship.
Attend games, tournaments, and other team events.
Communicate effectively with players, parents, and school administration.
Ensure the safety and well-being of all team members during practices and games.
Emphasize the importance of fair play and good sportsmanship.
Collaborate with other coaches and school staff to coordinate team activities.

Qualifications:
    Previous coaching experience, preferably in softball.
    In-depth knowledge of softball rules, techniques, and strategies.
    Strong leadership and communication skills.
    Ability to motivate and inspire student-athletes to reach their full potential.
    Patience, resilience, and a positive attitude.
    Willingness to undergo any necessary background checks or training.

Schedule:
The middle school softball season typically runs from February 3 to May 13. Practices are typically held Monday - Friday after school, with games scheduled on Tuesday and Thursdays.

Attachment(s):
Athletics Coach.pdf</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Athletics- High School/ Middle School Coaches</JobType>
    <Sport>Softball</Sport>
    <Location>Porter Ridge Middle</Location>
    <City>Porter Ridge</City>
    <State>NC</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience>Previous coaching experience, preferably in softball</Experience>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-06-24</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=14840</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=14840</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Porter Ridge Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Union County Public Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/ucps/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Porter Ridge Middle</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="ae8aab98-1b0f-45a9-95a7-fbce03d90bad" state="North Dakota" district="Dickison D1" districtId="Dickison D1" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:04:28+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head Girls Volleyball Coach- 6th Grade</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head Girls Volleyball Coach- 6th Grade role at Dickinson Middle School is focused on building a competitive, well‑organized program that still prioritizes the overall well‑being of student‑athletes. This position blends strategy, culture‑building, and teaching, providing the coach with an opportunity to influence the direction of the program for years to come. The successful candidate will bring a clear vision for how to teach the sport, how to manage a team, and how to represent the school in a positive and professional manner.

From a competitive standpoint, the Head Girls Volleyball Coach- 6th Grade is responsible for developing seasonal plans that align practice content, conditioning work, and game preparation. This includes designing practice segments that progress from individual fundamentals to full‑team tactical execution. The coach should be comfortable breaking down film, identifying areas for improvement, and communicating game plans in a way that athletes can understand and apply under pressure.

Equally important is the culture created by the coach. At Dickinson Middle School, teams are expected to demonstrate sportsmanship, respect, and unity. The Head Girls Volleyball Coach- 6th Grade sets standards for effort in practice, behavior in the classroom, and conduct in the community. That might involve establishing team guidelines, leading discussions about values, and recognizing athletes who demonstrate leadership or growth in those areas. The goal is to build a program where success is measured not just by wins and losses but by the quality of the experience for everyone involved.

This position also involves close coordination with the academic side of the school. The coach monitors eligibility, encourages students to keep up with assignments, and celebrates academic milestones. Communicating with teachers and counselors when necessary helps support student‑athletes as whole people, not just as performers in one activity. At Dickinson Middle School, the Head Girls Volleyball Coach- 6th Grade is viewed as part of the educational team.

Program administration tasks include managing equipment and uniforms, tracking inventory, assisting with scheduling, and following all district and league regulations. The coach should be organized, punctual, and attentive to details such as transportation arrangements and roster paperwork. Safety protocols, including emergency action planning and injury‑reporting procedures, must be consistently followed.

Overall, the Head Girls Volleyball Coach- 6th Grade at Dickinson Middle School is best suited for a coach who is excited about teaching, willing to collaborate with colleagues, and prepared to invest in the growth of student‑athletes over multiple seasons. It is an opportunity to provide structure, challenge, and support while representing the school with pride in the larger athletic community.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Girls Volleyball</Sport>
    <Location>Dickinson Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>ND</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>$2,757 - $3,257 DOE</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/dpsnd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=853</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/dpsnd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=853</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/dpsnd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/dpsnd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Dickinson Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Dickison D1 coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/dpsnd/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Dickinson Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="81a0089a-e851-4150-b1d2-c687f37a4a4b" state="Nebraska" district="Bellevue Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:12:16+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Baseball Coach 2025-2026 (BW)</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>Search Jobs
Jobs
Internal Jobs
About
Search
Reset
Show Map
coach
5 results
Sort by Date:
Track Coach 2025-2026 (MM)

Mission Middle School

Bellevue, Nebraska

Oct 03, 2025 5:00 AM (UTC)

Assistant Baseball Coach 2025-2026 (BW)

Bellevue West High School

Bellevue, Nebraska

Sep 15, 2025 5:00 AM (UTC)

Assistant Track Coach 2025-2026 (BE)

Bellevue East High School

Bellevue, Nebraska

Sep 03, 2025 5:00 AM (UTC)

Assistant Girls Basketball Coach 2025-2026 (BE)

Bellevue East High School

Bellevue, Nebraska

Aug 27, 2025 5:00 AM (UTC)

Assistant Cheer Coach 2025-2026 (BE)

Bellevue East High School

Bellevue, Nebraska

Aug 26, 2025 5:00 AM (UTC)

Assistant Baseball Coach 2025-2026 (BW)
Bellevue NE
Bellevue West High School - Bellevue, Nebraska Open in Google Maps
Job Details
Job ID:5374195
Application Deadline:Posted until filled
Posted:Sep 15, 2025 5:00 AM (UTC)

Starting Date:Immediately

Job Description

Bellevue West High School is accepting applications for an Assistant Baseball Coach.

 

All extracurricular positions promote the philosophy and goals of the district while assisting with the development of the particular program.  The position requires supervision of participants and the ability to communicate expectations to both participants and parents. Furthermore, serving as a liaison between participating parents, patrons, staff, and administration as needed as well as helping with the management of the operation by carrying out rules and regulations are essential. This position is subject to a veterans preference.

EQUAL OPPORTUNITY EMPLOYER

Position Type:Part-Time
Job Requirements
Contact Information
Map

The content you submit, offer, contribute, attach, post, or display (each a “Submission”) will be viewed by other users of the service who may or may not be accurately representing who they are or who they represent. Do not include any sensitive data in your submissions. Any submission or any use or reliance on any content or materials posted via the service or obtained by you through the use of the service is at your own risk. “Sensitive data” for purposes of this section means social security or other government-issued identification numbers, medical or health information, account security information, individual financial account information, credit/debit/gift or other payment card information, account passwords, individual credit and income information or any other sensitive personal data as defined under applicable laws.
© 2026 PowerSchool Group LLC and/or its affiliates. All trademarks are either owned or licensed by PowerSchool Group LLC or its affiliates.</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
    <Location>Bellevue, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Bellevue</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-09-15</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://bellevuene.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5374195</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://bellevuene.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5374195</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://bellevuene.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>personneldept@bpsne.net</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Bellevue West High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Bellevue Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://bellevuene.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Bellevue West High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="4b2b4c3b-9cfd-4bc5-898d-13902b0c8462" state="Nebraska" district="Fremont Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:16:30+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Activities - Co-Head Varsity Girls Soccer Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Activities - Co-Head Varsity Girls Soccer Coach position at Scott Anderson provides an opportunity to guide student‑athletes through an experience that combines challenge, support, and growth. This role is intended for coaches who see beyond wins and losses and who value the lasting impact that a positive athletic program can have on young people. Through careful planning, consistent expectations, and ongoing communication, the coach helps create a framework where athletes can thrive.

From an instructional perspective, the Activities - Co-Head Varsity Girls Soccer Coach prepares practices that sequence learning effectively. Early sessions may focus heavily on fundamentals and basic systems, while later practices refine execution and introduce more advanced concepts. The coach uses demonstrations, targeted drills, and guided scrimmages to help athletes apply what they learn. Regular assessment allows the coach to adjust plans based on the team’s progress.

The position also requires deliberate attention to team culture. At Scott Anderson, the Activities - Co-Head Varsity Girls Soccer Coach works to ensure that the environment is welcoming, fair, and focused on collective responsibility. The coach sets expectations around effort, communication, and respect, and follows through when those expectations are not met. Celebrating positive examples and giving athletes leadership opportunities strengthens the sense of ownership within the group.

Support for the broader student experience is built into the job. Coaches stay informed about academic calendars, test periods, and other school events so that practices and competitions are scheduled thoughtfully whenever possible. The Activities - Co-Head Varsity Girls Soccer Coach encourages athletes to communicate about conflicts in advance and to take initiative in managing their commitments. When students feel supported in both academics and athletics, they are more likely to remain engaged and successful.

Administrative responsibilities include coordination with the athletic department, assisting with transportation, submitting required paperwork, and maintaining accurate rosters. The coach must be attentive to detail and willing to complete these tasks reliably, as they directly affect the experience of athletes and families.

At its core, the Activities - Co-Head Varsity Girls Soccer Coach at Scott Anderson is a chance to teach, to mentor, and to build something that extends beyond a single season. Candidates who are motivated by the opportunity to help students grow through sport will find this position especially meaningful.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Varsity Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Soccer</Sport>
    <Location>Fremont, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Fremont</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>As Per Extra Duty Schedule</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-17</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Open Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5292264</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5292264</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>hr@fpsmail.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Scott Anderson</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Fremont Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Fremont Public Sch.</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="ca73ae76-14df-4f93-93bd-5840bdb622b2" state="Nebraska" district="Bennington Pub. Sch." districtId="Bennington Pub. Sch." active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:23:30+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach role at Bennington South Middle School emphasizes collaboration, consistency, and long‑term program development. This position is ideal for a coach who enjoys working as part of a broader athletic staff and who values building connections across grade levels and teams. The goal is to help create a smooth pathway for student‑athletes as they progress, while maintaining a recognizable identity and standard of excellence for the program.

In practical terms, the Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach coordinates closely with the athletic director and fellow coaches to align terminology, teaching priorities, and expectations. This might involve participating in coaching meetings, sharing practice plans, and adapting approaches so that athletes experience similar structures and messages at each level. At Bennington South Middle School, the program is strongest when coaches communicate and support one another.

Day‑to‑day responsibilities include designing practices that teach core skills, reinforcing team concepts, and preparing athletes for competition. The coach works to balance repetition with variety, ensuring that key fundamentals are constantly reinforced while athletes also experience new challenges. The Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach reviews performance with the team, helping athletes learn how to analyze both successes and mistakes in a constructive way.

The role extends into community and family engagement. Coaches represent Bennington South Middle School at games, parent meetings, and potential youth outreach events. The Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach may help host clinics or camps, encourage younger students to try the sport, and provide information about expectations to families who are new to the program. A welcoming, organized presence can greatly influence how the program is perceived.

Athlete support is ongoing. The Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach monitors team morale, assists students in managing the demands of school and sport, and reinforces the importance of rest, nutrition, and healthy habits. The coach keeps the focus on sustainable growth rather than shortcuts, emphasizing that consistent effort over time leads to meaningful improvement.

Administrative tasks such as roster management, schedule communication, and equipment oversight are also part of the position. The Middle School Girls' Wrestling Coach must handle these responsibilities reliably, as they are essential to maintaining a well‑run program. Coaches who enjoy seeing the big picture, who are willing to share ideas, and who care about the experience of every athlete will thrive in this role at Bennington South Middle School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>Bennington South Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://benningtonschools.schoolspring.com/?jobid=4802026</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://benningtonschools.schoolspring.com/?jobid=4802026</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://benningtonschools.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://benningtonschools.schoolspring.com/</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Bennington South Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Bennington Pub. Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://benningtonschools.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Bennington South Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="66a88dda-4c91-4f19-bd56-8f84e4302b27" state="Nebraska" district="Millard Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:30:54+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Girls Basketball Coach at Millard North High School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Assistant Girls Basketball Coach at Millard North High School at Millard North High School is a comprehensive coaching role that combines instruction, mentorship, and program management. This long‑form description reflects the multifaceted nature of school coaching, where the coach is both a technical expert and a caring adult presence in the lives of student‑athletes. The position is ideal for someone who values structure, communication, and collaboration while maintaining a clear focus on student development.

Day to day, the Assistant Girls Basketball Coach at Millard North High School plans and leads practices that prioritize safety, learning, and steady improvement. A typical session might include dynamic warm‑ups, small‑group drills, competitive games, and review conversations that help athletes understand why they are working on certain skills. The coach explains expectations clearly, uses age‑appropriate language, and adapts instruction so that athletes at different experience levels can participate and progress.

Another key element of the job is fostering positive habits. Coaches at Millard North High School reinforce punctuality, preparedness, and respectful communication. The Assistant Girls Basketball Coach at Millard North High School expects athletes to bring the proper equipment, to listen when others are speaking, and to take responsibility for their effort and behavior. When mistakes occur, the coach responds with guidance and accountability rather than embarrassment, reinforcing that learning is an ongoing process.

The role also emphasizes alignment with the school’s mission. Athletics is treated as part of the educational program, not as a separate or higher priority. That means the Assistant Girls Basketball Coach at Millard North High School supports academic expectations, respects teachers’ roles, and encourages athletes to manage their time effectively. By checking in on grades and reinforcing eligibility requirements, the coach helps students see the connection between their everyday decisions and their opportunities to compete.

Operationally, the position involves logistics such as coordinating with transportation, ensuring facilities are left in good condition, communicating schedules, and maintaining equipment inventories. The coach understands district policies, league rules, and safety procedures, and follows them consistently. Maintaining required certifications and participating in professional development keeps the coach informed about best practices in training and athlete welfare.

In addition, the Assistant Girls Basketball Coach at Millard North High School may contribute to long‑term program building through youth clinics, off‑season activities, and collaboration with other levels of the program. By investing in relationships with families and younger athletes, the coach helps sustain interest and continuity in the sport at Millard North High School. Candidates who enjoy balancing big‑picture planning with day‑to‑day teaching will find this position engaging and fulfilling.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Part-Time</JobType>
    <Sport>Basketball</Sport>
    <Location>Omaha, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Omaha</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2026-01-02</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2026-01-16</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://millard.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5483886</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://millard.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5483886</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://millard.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>cmalberico@mpsomaha.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Millard North High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Millard Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://millard.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Millard North High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="fdb3edfb-14c9-4049-9923-22317aac2167" state="Nebraska" district="Fremont Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:38:06+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Activities - Head Girls Track Coach - Middle School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Activities - Head Girls Track Coach - Middle School at Middle School is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Activities - Head Girls Track Coach - Middle School manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Middle School, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Activities - Head Girls Track Coach - Middle School demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Activities - Head Girls Track Coach - Middle School follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Activities - Head Girls Track Coach - Middle School at Middle School allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Track &amp; Field</Sport>
    <Location>Middle School - Fremont, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Fremont</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>As Per Extra Duty Schedule</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-01</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Open Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5265555</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5265555</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>hr@fpsmail.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Fremont Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="8c4b4e03-dce7-4572-acc2-f44cb040f28d" state="Nebraska" district="Fremont Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:38:06+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Activities - 7/8 Assistant Football Coach - Middle School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Activities - 7/8 Assistant Football Coach - Middle School at Middle School is a comprehensive coaching role that combines instruction, mentorship, and program management. This long‑form description reflects the multifaceted nature of school coaching, where the coach is both a technical expert and a caring adult presence in the lives of student‑athletes. The position is ideal for someone who values structure, communication, and collaboration while maintaining a clear focus on student development.

Day to day, the Activities - 7/8 Assistant Football Coach - Middle School plans and leads practices that prioritize safety, learning, and steady improvement. A typical session might include dynamic warm‑ups, small‑group drills, competitive games, and review conversations that help athletes understand why they are working on certain skills. The coach explains expectations clearly, uses age‑appropriate language, and adapts instruction so that athletes at different experience levels can participate and progress.

Another key element of the job is fostering positive habits. Coaches at Middle School reinforce punctuality, preparedness, and respectful communication. The Activities - 7/8 Assistant Football Coach - Middle School expects athletes to bring the proper equipment, to listen when others are speaking, and to take responsibility for their effort and behavior. When mistakes occur, the coach responds with guidance and accountability rather than embarrassment, reinforcing that learning is an ongoing process.

The role also emphasizes alignment with the school’s mission. Athletics is treated as part of the educational program, not as a separate or higher priority. That means the Activities - 7/8 Assistant Football Coach - Middle School supports academic expectations, respects teachers’ roles, and encourages athletes to manage their time effectively. By checking in on grades and reinforcing eligibility requirements, the coach helps students see the connection between their everyday decisions and their opportunities to compete.

Operationally, the position involves logistics such as coordinating with transportation, ensuring facilities are left in good condition, communicating schedules, and maintaining equipment inventories. The coach understands district policies, league rules, and safety procedures, and follows them consistently. Maintaining required certifications and participating in professional development keeps the coach informed about best practices in training and athlete welfare.

In addition, the Activities - 7/8 Assistant Football Coach - Middle School may contribute to long‑term program building through youth clinics, off‑season activities, and collaboration with other levels of the program. By investing in relationships with families and younger athletes, the coach helps sustain interest and continuity in the sport at Middle School. Candidates who enjoy balancing big‑picture planning with day‑to‑day teaching will find this position engaging and fulfilling.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Part-Time</JobType>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
    <Location>Middle School - Fremont, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Fremont</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>As Per Extra Duty Schedule</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-05-19</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Open Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5176888</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5176888</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>hr@fpsmail.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Fremont Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="87bf87ea-3e7f-43a0-8a33-d6f51d0caca2" state="Nebraska" district="Fremont Public Sch." districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:38:06+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School position at Middle School is an opportunity to shape a positive, inclusive, and hardworking team environment where students learn to love their sport and take pride in representing their school. This role emphasizes relationship‑building, clear expectations, and steady improvement over the course of a season and across multiple years of participation. The coach serves as a daily presence in the lives of student‑athletes, modeling the type of attitude and work ethic that leads to both athletic and personal growth.

At the core of the job is teaching. The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School is responsible for breaking down complex skills into manageable steps, offering demonstrations, and creating drills that allow athletes to practice safely and effectively. Practices should be organized around clear objectives, with time built in for warm‑up, instruction, repetition, and review. The coach gives frequent feedback, adjusts activities based on what athletes need, and encourages questions so that students remain engaged in their learning.

The role also involves nurturing team chemistry and a sense of belonging. At Middle School, coaches work to make sure every athlete feels included and respected. That means setting guidelines that prevent negative behavior, addressing conflicts quickly and fairly, and celebrating contributions from both starters and role players. The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School encourages athletes to support one another, communicate openly, and take pride in representing their school with class.

Beyond the field, court, track, or pool, the coach collaborates with school staff to support student‑athletes as whole people. That includes reinforcing academic expectations, respecting school policies, and helping students manage the demands of both athletics and coursework. Regular contact with families keeps everyone informed about schedules, expectations, and program goals, and offers a consistent channel for questions or concerns.

The Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School also participates in broader program responsibilities such as attending department meetings, assisting with youth outreach or clinics, and contributing to long‑term planning. The coach is expected to stay current with best practices in training, injury prevention, and sport‑specific strategy, and to maintain any certifications required by the district or state association.

For individuals who enjoy working with young people, who believe in the value of school‑based athletics, and who are prepared to invest time in building a healthy team culture, the Activities - Assistant Football Coach - Middle School role at Middle School is a meaningful and impactful opportunity.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
    <Location>Middle School - Fremont, Nebraska</Location>
    <City>Fremont</City>
    <State>NE</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>As Per Extra Duty Schedule</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-01</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Open Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5265563</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/?jobid=5265563</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>hr@fpsmail.org</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Fremont Public Sch. coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://fps.schoolspring.com/</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="8682bc95-f901-42ac-a24e-e0ea94138d2c" state="New Hampshire" district="Keene School District" districtId="Keene School District" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-07T10:48:13+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Girls Middle School Basketball Coach - Chesterfield School 2025</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Girls Middle School Basketball Coach - Chesterfield School 2025 at Chesterfield School is a high‑engagement coaching role that calls for energy, clear communication, and a steady presence for student‑athletes. This position is built for a coach who enjoys being actively involved in every aspect of the program, from leading warm‑ups and teaching tactics to meeting with families and coordinating logistics. The coach is expected to bring consistency and enthusiasm to each interaction with the team.

Practices led by the Girls Middle School Basketball Coach - Chesterfield School 2025 are structured and purposeful. They begin with appropriate warm‑ups, transition into focused skill work, and conclude with competitive or situational activities that resemble live play. The coach introduces concepts in manageable steps and checks for understanding, encouraging athletes to ask questions and learn the reasoning behind drills and strategies. This approach helps athletes become smarter, more confident players.

Motivation is another key component of the job. Coaches at Chesterfield School use positive reinforcement, high yet realistic expectations, and clear feedback to help athletes push themselves. The Girls Middle School Basketball Coach - Chesterfield School 2025 recognizes effort and improvement, not just outcomes, and supports athletes through setbacks. This creates an environment where students are willing to take risks and grow.

The role also includes a strong communication element. The coach keeps families informed about schedules, travel, and program expectations, and responds to questions in a respectful, timely manner. Within the school, the Girls Middle School Basketball Coach - Chesterfield School 2025 collaborates with administrators and teachers to support students’ academic responsibilities, reinforcing that success in the classroom is essential.

Finally, the position requires adherence to safety and policy standards. The Girls Middle School Basketball Coach - Chesterfield School 2025 maintains appropriate supervision ratios, follows guidelines on equipment use, and ensures that emergency procedures are understood and practiced. The coach models appropriate conduct toward officials and opponents, reinforcing that competing with integrity is a core expectation at Chesterfield School. This comprehensive role is well suited to coaches who are organized, student‑focused, and eager to contribute to a strong athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Coaching Staff</JobType>
    <Sport>Girls Basketball</Sport>
    <Location>Chesterfield School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>NH</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate>Until Filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/sau29/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=6071</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/sau29/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=6071</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/sau29/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/sau29/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Chesterfield School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Keene School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/sau29/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Chesterfield School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="c692b11d-c276-47ec-970f-e479e5afa341" state="Michigan" district="Plymouth-Canton Community Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-14T07:22:54+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Boys Lacrosse – Head JV Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>The Boys Lacrosse – Head JV Coach position at PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL provides an opportunity to guide student‑athletes through an experience that combines challenge, support, and growth. This role is intended for coaches who see beyond wins and losses and who value the lasting impact that a positive athletic program can have on young people. Through careful planning, consistent expectations, and ongoing communication, the coach helps create a framework where athletes can thrive.

From an instructional perspective, the Boys Lacrosse – Head JV Coach prepares practices that sequence learning effectively. Early sessions may focus heavily on fundamentals and basic systems, while later practices refine execution and introduce more advanced concepts. The coach uses demonstrations, targeted drills, and guided scrimmages to help athletes apply what they learn. Regular assessment allows the coach to adjust plans based on the team’s progress.

The position also requires deliberate attention to team culture. At PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL, the Boys Lacrosse – Head JV Coach works to ensure that the environment is welcoming, fair, and focused on collective responsibility. The coach sets expectations around effort, communication, and respect, and follows through when those expectations are not met. Celebrating positive examples and giving athletes leadership opportunities strengthens the sense of ownership within the group.

Support for the broader student experience is built into the job. Coaches stay informed about academic calendars, test periods, and other school events so that practices and competitions are scheduled thoughtfully whenever possible. The Boys Lacrosse – Head JV Coach encourages athletes to communicate about conflicts in advance and to take initiative in managing their commitments. When students feel supported in both academics and athletics, they are more likely to remain engaged and successful.

Administrative responsibilities include coordination with the athletic department, assisting with transportation, submitting required paperwork, and maintaining accurate rosters. The coach must be attentive to detail and willing to complete these tasks reliably, as they directly affect the experience of athletes and families.

At its core, the Boys Lacrosse – Head JV Coach at PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL is a chance to teach, to mentor, and to build something that extends beyond a single season. Candidates who are motivated by the opportunity to help students grow through sport will find this position especially meaningful.</JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head JV Coach</JobType>
    <Sport>Lacrosse</Sport>
    <Location>PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL</Location>
    <City>Plymouth</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>According to the Master Agreement - Schedule “B”</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-17</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1293</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1293</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Plymouth-Canton Community Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="0fe75160-79c8-4256-850e-c98a591fa229" state="Michigan" district="Plymouth-Canton Community Schools" districtId="" active="false" lastSeen="2026-01-14T07:22:54+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Boys Lacrosse - Head JV Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>MINIMUM QUALIFICATIONS:
1. High school graduate or equivalent
2. Applicants must have experience in high school level coaching or playing at college or university level in sport to which they are applying.
3. Applicant must have a time schedule compatible with that of the high school.
4. CPR and/or first aide training preferred.
5. Applicants willing to coach additional high school sports are preferred.
6. Demonstrated ability to work with parents and children.
REPORTS TO: Assistant Principal of Activities and Athletics
RATE OF PAY: According to the Master Agreement - Schedule "B"
BEGINNING DATE: 2025/2026 Spring season
DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:
1. The coach will be responsible for the entire organization of the sport to which he/she is assigned.
2. The coach will be directly responsible for all equipment in his/her sport. A complete inventory of all equipment will be filed with the director at the end of each season.
3. The coach will be responsible for all awards presented in his/her sport and a season summary.
4. Bending, lifting, and overhead work required.
5. Performs other tasks as assigned.
This description is intended to describe the essential job functions, the general supplemental functions and the essential requirements for the performance of this job. It is not an exhaustive list of all duties, responsibilities and requirements of a person so classified. Other functions may be assigned and management retains the right to add or change the duties at any time.
EVALUATION: Performance of this position will be evaluated annually.
METHOD OF APPLICATION: Internal and external applicants should complete the online application in the Frontline system.
External applicants will be hired and paid by EDUstaff. www.EDUstaff.orgPOSTINGS WILL BE EFFECTIVE FOR 5 WORKING DAYS
DEADLINE FOR APPLICATION: Open until filled</JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Lacrosse</Sport>
    <Location>PLYMOUTH HIGH SCHOOL</Location>
    <City>Canton</City>
    <State>MI</State>
    <Country>USA</Country>
    <ZipCode>48187</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange>Contact for Details</SalaryRange>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-07-17</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>Until filled</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1293</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=1293</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail>Chechaka.johnson@pccsk12.com</EmployerEmail>
    <EmployerFullName>Plymouth High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Plymouth-Canton Community Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail>https://www.applitrack.com/pccsk12/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=COACH</CompanyEmail>
    <CompanyName>Plymouth High School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
</Jobs>