<?xml version='1.0' encoding='UTF-8'?>
<Jobs>
  <Job id="6a28bc59-e0d6-4ee4-b8f9-4aef7bf6fdb2" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:40:59+00:00">
    <JobTitle>8th Grade Head Football Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The 8th Grade Head Football Coach position at Finland Middle is an opportunity to shape a positive, inclusive, and hardworking team environment where students learn to love their sport and take pride in representing their school. This role emphasizes relationship‑building, clear expectations, and steady improvement over the course of a season and across multiple years of participation. The coach serves as a daily presence in the lives of student‑athletes, modeling the type of attitude and work ethic that leads to both athletic and personal growth.

At the core of the job is teaching. The 8th Grade Head Football Coach is responsible for breaking down complex skills into manageable steps, offering demonstrations, and creating drills that allow athletes to practice safely and effectively. Practices should be organized around clear objectives, with time built in for warm‑up, instruction, repetition, and review. The coach gives frequent feedback, adjusts activities based on what athletes need, and encourages questions so that students remain engaged in their learning.

The role also involves nurturing team chemistry and a sense of belonging. At Finland Middle, coaches work to make sure every athlete feels included and respected. That means setting guidelines that prevent negative behavior, addressing conflicts quickly and fairly, and celebrating contributions from both starters and role players. The 8th Grade Head Football Coach encourages athletes to support one another, communicate openly, and take pride in representing their school with class.

Beyond the field, court, track, or pool, the coach collaborates with school staff to support student‑athletes as whole people. That includes reinforcing academic expectations, respecting school policies, and helping students manage the demands of both athletics and coursework. Regular contact with families keeps everyone informed about schedules, expectations, and program goals, and offers a consistent channel for questions or concerns.

The 8th Grade Head Football Coach also participates in broader program responsibilities such as attending department meetings, assisting with youth outreach or clinics, and contributing to long‑term planning. The coach is expected to stay current with best practices in training, injury prevention, and sport‑specific strategy, and to maintain any certifications required by the district or state association.

For individuals who enjoy working with young people, who believe in the value of school‑based athletics, and who are prepared to invest time in building a healthy team culture, the 8th Grade Head Football Coach role at Finland Middle is a meaningful and impactful opportunity.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Finland Middle</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21832</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21832</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Finland Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Finland Middle</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="860c4903-8852-44d0-bd4d-d1410879078e" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-10-30T02:26:05+00:00">
    <JobTitle>8th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The 8th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach at Finland Middle is a comprehensive coaching role that combines instruction, mentorship, and program management. This long‑form description reflects the multifaceted nature of school coaching, where the coach is both a technical expert and a caring adult presence in the lives of student‑athletes. The position is ideal for someone who values structure, communication, and collaboration while maintaining a clear focus on student development.

Day to day, the 8th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach plans and leads practices that prioritize safety, learning, and steady improvement. A typical session might include dynamic warm‑ups, small‑group drills, competitive games, and review conversations that help athletes understand why they are working on certain skills. The coach explains expectations clearly, uses age‑appropriate language, and adapts instruction so that athletes at different experience levels can participate and progress.

Another key element of the job is fostering positive habits. Coaches at Finland Middle reinforce punctuality, preparedness, and respectful communication. The 8th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach expects athletes to bring the proper equipment, to listen when others are speaking, and to take responsibility for their effort and behavior. When mistakes occur, the coach responds with guidance and accountability rather than embarrassment, reinforcing that learning is an ongoing process.

The role also emphasizes alignment with the school’s mission. Athletics is treated as part of the educational program, not as a separate or higher priority. That means the 8th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach supports academic expectations, respects teachers’ roles, and encourages athletes to manage their time effectively. By checking in on grades and reinforcing eligibility requirements, the coach helps students see the connection between their everyday decisions and their opportunities to compete.

Operationally, the position involves logistics such as coordinating with transportation, ensuring facilities are left in good condition, communicating schedules, and maintaining equipment inventories. The coach understands district policies, league rules, and safety procedures, and follows them consistently. Maintaining required certifications and participating in professional development keeps the coach informed about best practices in training and athlete welfare.

In addition, the 8th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach may contribute to long‑term program building through youth clinics, off‑season activities, and collaboration with other levels of the program. By investing in relationships with families and younger athletes, the coach helps sustain interest and continuity in the sport at Finland Middle. Candidates who enjoy balancing big‑picture planning with day‑to‑day teaching will find this position engaging and fulfilling.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Finland Middle</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>hhttps://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21834</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21834</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Finland Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Finland Middle</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Basketball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="5479d3a4-ef7c-4abb-b5cf-08ce2611398c" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:41:07+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head Wrestling Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head Wrestling Coach at Finland Middle is a high‑engagement coaching role that calls for energy, clear communication, and a steady presence for student‑athletes. This position is built for a coach who enjoys being actively involved in every aspect of the program, from leading warm‑ups and teaching tactics to meeting with families and coordinating logistics. The coach is expected to bring consistency and enthusiasm to each interaction with the team.

Practices led by the Head Wrestling Coach are structured and purposeful. They begin with appropriate warm‑ups, transition into focused skill work, and conclude with competitive or situational activities that resemble live play. The coach introduces concepts in manageable steps and checks for understanding, encouraging athletes to ask questions and learn the reasoning behind drills and strategies. This approach helps athletes become smarter, more confident players.

Motivation is another key component of the job. Coaches at Finland Middle use positive reinforcement, high yet realistic expectations, and clear feedback to help athletes push themselves. The Head Wrestling Coach recognizes effort and improvement, not just outcomes, and supports athletes through setbacks. This creates an environment where students are willing to take risks and grow.

The role also includes a strong communication element. The coach keeps families informed about schedules, travel, and program expectations, and responds to questions in a respectful, timely manner. Within the school, the Head Wrestling Coach collaborates with administrators and teachers to support students’ academic responsibilities, reinforcing that success in the classroom is essential.

Finally, the position requires adherence to safety and policy standards. The Head Wrestling Coach maintains appropriate supervision ratios, follows guidelines on equipment use, and ensures that emergency procedures are understood and practiced. The coach models appropriate conduct toward officials and opponents, reinforcing that competing with integrity is a core expectation at Finland Middle. This comprehensive role is well suited to coaches who are organized, student‑focused, and eager to contribute to a strong athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Finland Middle</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21836</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21836</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Finland Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Finland Middle</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="938c57ca-fa58-44e5-a16e-4679a8c3b6a3" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:41:15+00:00">
    <JobTitle>7th Grade Head Football Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The 7th Grade Head Football Coach at Pleasant View Middle is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the 7th Grade Head Football Coach is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At Pleasant View Middle, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The 7th Grade Head Football Coach helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The 7th Grade Head Football Coach works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at Pleasant View Middle operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent Pleasant View Middle with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the 7th Grade Head Football Coach reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the 7th Grade Head Football Coach role at Pleasant View Middle.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Pleasant View Middle</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21844</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21844</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Pleasant View Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Pleasant View Middle</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="e36f549a-37f5-44b5-8959-e3aa2b42d222" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:41:23+00:00">
    <JobTitle>7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The 7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach position at Pleasant View Middle is a key leadership role within the school's athletic program and wider learning community. This long-form description is designed to give prospective applicants a clear view of the expectations, responsibilities, and culture that surround the role. Coaches in this position are trusted to model character, support academic success, and help student‑athletes grow through meaningful experiences in practice, competition, and daily school life.

In this role, the 7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach works closely with the athletic director, school administrators, and other coaches to design and maintain a structured, developmentally appropriate program. That includes planning practices that blend fundamental skill instruction, competitive drills, and situational teaching so athletes understand both the technical and strategic sides of the game. The coach is responsible for teaching core skills, reinforcing proper technique, and helping athletes safely build strength, conditioning, and sport‑specific endurance.

The position also focuses heavily on culture and leadership. The 7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach at Pleasant View Middle sets the tone for effort, respect, and sportsmanship. This involves building clear expectations for behavior, guiding athletes through wins and losses with perspective, and maintaining standards that reflect the values of the school and community. Student‑athletes should come away from the program with improved confidence, stronger communication skills, and a better understanding of teamwork and accountability.

Another important part of the job is collaboration. The coach regularly communicates with teachers, counselors, and families to help student‑athletes balance athletics with academics and other responsibilities. At Pleasant View Middle, athletic participation is viewed as an extension of the classroom rather than a replacement for it. The 7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach encourages students to stay organized, meet eligibility requirements, and pursue long‑term goals in the classroom as well as on the field or court.

Program operations also fall under this role. The coach helps manage equipment, uniforms, and facilities, and assists with scheduling, transportation coordination, and adherence to league and district policies. The 7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach is expected to understand and follow all relevant regulations, including eligibility rules, sportsmanship guidelines, and safety standards, while maintaining current certifications such as CPR/First Aid as required by the district.

Finally, the 7th Grade Girls Head Basketball Coach position at Pleasant View Middle is a visible role that represents the school within the larger community. The coach interacts with families, officials, visiting teams, and youth programs, modeling professionalism in every setting. Candidates who are passionate about teaching, committed to student growth, and prepared to invest time and energy into the long‑term health of the program will find this role both challenging and rewarding.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Pleasant View Middle</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21845</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21845</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Pleasant View Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Pleasant View Middle</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Basketball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="526be054-52db-457c-b79f-48f4f2e33a5c" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:41:31+00:00">
    <JobTitle>7th Grade Boys Head Basketball Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The 7th Grade Boys Head Basketball Coach at Pleasant View Middle is a high‑engagement coaching role that calls for energy, clear communication, and a steady presence for student‑athletes. This position is built for a coach who enjoys being actively involved in every aspect of the program, from leading warm‑ups and teaching tactics to meeting with families and coordinating logistics. The coach is expected to bring consistency and enthusiasm to each interaction with the team.

Practices led by the 7th Grade Boys Head Basketball Coach are structured and purposeful. They begin with appropriate warm‑ups, transition into focused skill work, and conclude with competitive or situational activities that resemble live play. The coach introduces concepts in manageable steps and checks for understanding, encouraging athletes to ask questions and learn the reasoning behind drills and strategies. This approach helps athletes become smarter, more confident players.

Motivation is another key component of the job. Coaches at Pleasant View Middle use positive reinforcement, high yet realistic expectations, and clear feedback to help athletes push themselves. The 7th Grade Boys Head Basketball Coach recognizes effort and improvement, not just outcomes, and supports athletes through setbacks. This creates an environment where students are willing to take risks and grow.

The role also includes a strong communication element. The coach keeps families informed about schedules, travel, and program expectations, and responds to questions in a respectful, timely manner. Within the school, the 7th Grade Boys Head Basketball Coach collaborates with administrators and teachers to support students’ academic responsibilities, reinforcing that success in the classroom is essential.

Finally, the position requires adherence to safety and policy standards. The 7th Grade Boys Head Basketball Coach maintains appropriate supervision ratios, follows guidelines on equipment use, and ensures that emergency procedures are understood and practiced. The coach models appropriate conduct toward officials and opponents, reinforcing that competing with integrity is a core expectation at Pleasant View Middle. This comprehensive role is well suited to coaches who are organized, student‑focused, and eager to contribute to a strong athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Pleasant View Middle</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21847</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21847</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Pleasant View Middle</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Pleasant View Middle</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Basketball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="6f02b7d4-6ba8-4fba-b053-dd5495b7b615" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:41:38+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head Cross Country Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head Cross Country Coach at Central Crossing High School is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Head Cross Country Coach is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At Central Crossing High School, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Head Cross Country Coach helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Head Cross Country Coach works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at Central Crossing High School operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent Central Crossing High School with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Head Cross Country Coach reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Head Cross Country Coach role at Central Crossing High School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Central Crossing High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21849</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21849</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Central Crossing High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Central Crossing High School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Cross Country</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="1adb8609-e001-4ac0-9630-4539a3bd26a6" state="Ohio" district="South-Western City School District" districtId="South-Western City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:41:47+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head Swimming Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head Swimming Coach at Central Crossing High School is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Head Swimming Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Central Crossing High School, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Head Swimming Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Head Swimming Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Head Swimming Coach at Central Crossing High School allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Central Crossing High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-13</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21854</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=21854</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://phl.applitrack.com/duesc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?all=1&amp;AppliTrackPostingSearch=title%3Acoach%20&amp;AppliTrackZipRadius=5&amp;AppliTrackLayoutMode=detail</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Central Crossing High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>South-Western City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Central Crossing High School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Swimming and Diving</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="840006bb-bcae-4169-ae55-84da914aaafc" state="Ohio" district="Dublin City Schools" districtId="Dublin City Schools" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:42:02+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Coach (Title Unconfirmed)</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Coach (Title Unconfirmed) at Dublin is an integral member of the school's educational team, using athletics as a platform for teaching discipline, teamwork, and perseverance. This position calls for a coach who is organized, reflective, and committed to continuous improvement, both for themselves and for their athletes. The role blends hands‑on coaching with program administration and relationship‑building.

From a coaching standpoint, the Coach (Title Unconfirmed) is responsible for teaching the rules, techniques, and strategies of the sport in a way that is accessible to student‑athletes. Practices are planned to include progressive skill work, position‑specific instruction, and opportunities for athletes to apply learning in controlled scrimmage situations. The coach pays attention to pacing and variety so that sessions remain engaging while still challenging students to stretch their comfort zones.

Culture is a central focus of this job. At Dublin, the Coach (Title Unconfirmed) helps create a team environment where respect, honesty, and effort are expected. The coach sets clear standards regarding communication, attendance, and sportsmanship, and works with athletes to understand why these standards matter. When expectations are not met, the coach responds fairly, explaining consequences and encouraging athletes to learn from mistakes.

The position also requires responsiveness to student needs. Coaches remain aware of the emotional and academic pressures students face and adjust support accordingly. Checking in with athletes, acknowledging their efforts, and partnering with school staff all contribute to a positive experience. The Coach (Title Unconfirmed) may assist in connecting students with resources when additional support is needed.

Outside of direct coaching, the role involves tasks such as coordinating with officials and opponents, assisting with scheduling, and managing team communication channels. The coach must be punctual, prepared, and detail‑oriented, ensuring that events run smoothly and that the team represents Dublin well at home and away.

Safety remains an ongoing responsibility. The Coach (Title Unconfirmed) follows district guidelines, maintains necessary certifications, and emphasizes proper warm‑up routines and technique to minimize risk of injury. This comprehensive approach to coaching allows student‑athletes to pursue their goals in a structured environment that prioritizes learning, well‑being, and long‑term success.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Dublin, OH</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-10-30</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Dublin</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Dublin City Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Dublin City Schools</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="cecd10ca-5b0e-44b9-a6fe-45600def5c72" state="Ohio" district="Dublin City Schools" districtId="Dublin City Schools" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:42:17+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Head JV Girls Golf Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Head JV Girls Golf Coach at Dublin is designed for a coach who believes that athletics is a powerful tool for teaching life skills. This role centers on developing student‑athletes as people first and competitors second, helping them learn responsibility, perseverance, and teamwork in a structured and supportive environment. The program places a strong emphasis on clear communication, mutual respect, and long‑term development rather than short‑term results alone.

On a daily basis, the Head JV Girls Golf Coach is responsible for planning and delivering practices that are active, safe, and inclusive. Training sessions should include a balance of fundamentals, decision‑making drills, and live or game‑like situations so that athletes are constantly learning. The coach provides direct instruction, demonstrates proper technique, and offers individualized feedback to help each athlete progress from their current skill level.

In addition to technical coaching, this position carries significant mentoring responsibilities. At Dublin, coaches are expected to build positive relationships with student‑athletes and to support them through the challenges of school, competition, and adolescence. That means listening carefully, encouraging good choices, and reinforcing expectations related to attendance, academic effort, and personal conduct. The Head JV Girls Golf Coach helps create a team environment where athletes feel valued and where they understand that their actions affect the group.

The role also includes collaboration with the broader athletic department. The Head JV Girls Golf Coach works with the athletic director and other coaches to coordinate facility use, align program philosophies, and support multi‑sport participation when possible. Sharing information, attending department meetings, and contributing to school‑wide initiatives all help ensure that the program at Dublin operates smoothly and consistently from season to season.

Game‑day responsibilities include preparing athletes physically and mentally, organizing lineups, communicating adjustments, and modeling composure in competitive situations. The coach is expected to represent Dublin with professionalism toward officials, opponents, and fans. After competitions, the Head JV Girls Golf Coach reviews performance with the team, highlighting effort, improvement, and areas for growth.

Health and safety are a constant priority. The coach follows district and state guidelines for equipment use, conditioning progressions, and emergency response. Maintaining appropriate certifications and staying current with best practices helps ensure that every training and competition environment is as safe as possible for all participants. Candidates who care deeply about student development, enjoy teaching the details of the sport, and are committed to a positive, educational approach to athletics will be strong fits for the Head JV Girls Golf Coach role at Dublin.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head JV Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Dublin, OH</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-10-30</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Dublin</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Dublin City Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Dublin City Schools</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Golf</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="1b0d654d-257e-4492-a407-6930978bfdf6" state="Ohio" district="Dublin City Schools" districtId="Dublin City Schools" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:42:31+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Varsity Swimming Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Assistant Varsity Swimming Coach position at Dublin is an opportunity to shape a positive, inclusive, and hardworking team environment where students learn to love their sport and take pride in representing their school. This role emphasizes relationship‑building, clear expectations, and steady improvement over the course of a season and across multiple years of participation. The coach serves as a daily presence in the lives of student‑athletes, modeling the type of attitude and work ethic that leads to both athletic and personal growth.

At the core of the job is teaching. The Assistant Varsity Swimming Coach is responsible for breaking down complex skills into manageable steps, offering demonstrations, and creating drills that allow athletes to practice safely and effectively. Practices should be organized around clear objectives, with time built in for warm‑up, instruction, repetition, and review. The coach gives frequent feedback, adjusts activities based on what athletes need, and encourages questions so that students remain engaged in their learning.

The role also involves nurturing team chemistry and a sense of belonging. At Dublin, coaches work to make sure every athlete feels included and respected. That means setting guidelines that prevent negative behavior, addressing conflicts quickly and fairly, and celebrating contributions from both starters and role players. The Assistant Varsity Swimming Coach encourages athletes to support one another, communicate openly, and take pride in representing their school with class.

Beyond the field, court, track, or pool, the coach collaborates with school staff to support student‑athletes as whole people. That includes reinforcing academic expectations, respecting school policies, and helping students manage the demands of both athletics and coursework. Regular contact with families keeps everyone informed about schedules, expectations, and program goals, and offers a consistent channel for questions or concerns.

The Assistant Varsity Swimming Coach also participates in broader program responsibilities such as attending department meetings, assisting with youth outreach or clinics, and contributing to long‑term planning. The coach is expected to stay current with best practices in training, injury prevention, and sport‑specific strategy, and to maintain any certifications required by the district or state association.

For individuals who enjoy working with young people, who believe in the value of school‑based athletics, and who are prepared to invest time in building a healthy team culture, the Assistant Varsity Swimming Coach role at Dublin is a meaningful and impactful opportunity.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Varsity Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Dublin, OH</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-10-30</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Dublin</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Dublin City Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Dublin City Schools</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Swimming and Diving</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="87221ef0-92f8-4dde-b365-0a5088a032bd" state="Ohio" district="Dublin City Schools" districtId="Dublin City Schools" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:42:44+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Boys Golf Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Boys Golf Coach role at Dublin is focused on helping student‑athletes unlock their potential through intentional coaching, structured practice environments, and a strong emphasis on character. This description outlines a position in which the coach is expected to be a planner, a teacher, a mentor, and a positive representative of the school community. Successful candidates bring energy to practices, patience to instruction, and clarity to expectations.

Practices form the backbone of the program, and the Boys Golf Coach is responsible for designing sessions that are purposeful and efficient. Each practice should have defined goals, from teaching new concepts to reinforcing previously learned skills or preparing for upcoming competition. The coach uses a variety of drills and teaching methods to keep athletes engaged, and regularly evaluates whether the team is progressing in the desired areas.

Coaches at Dublin are also trusted to guide student‑athletes through challenges. That can include addressing frustrations after a tough loss, helping a student handle the pressure of increased responsibility, or supporting someone who is balancing school, family, and activities. The Boys Golf Coach listens, provides perspective, and reinforces the idea that effort, attitude, and resilience are as important as any statistical outcome.

Communication is a key strength of this position. The coach shares information about schedules, team policies, and expectations with families and staff in a timely and professional way. Within the team, the Boys Golf Coach encourages athletes to ask questions, give feedback, and support one another. This open communication helps prevent misunderstandings and builds trust.

Safety and compliance cannot be overlooked. The Boys Golf Coach follows all relevant policies regarding equipment, supervision, travel, and emergency procedures. The coach maintains current certifications as required and keeps up with best practices around conditioning, concussion awareness, and hydration. At Dublin, the well‑being of student‑athletes is non‑negotiable.

This role is a good match for coaches who appreciate structure, care deeply about students, and are committed to building a consistent, values‑driven program. By serving as the Boys Golf Coach at Dublin, a coach has the opportunity to make a lasting impact on young people while contributing to a respected and sustainable athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Dublin, OH</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-10-30</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.dublinschools.net/departments/humanresources/current-openings/athleticsupplemental</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Dublin</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Dublin City Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Dublin City Schools</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Golf</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="6cb32730-3510-46bd-b11b-4e0af1db33e1" state="Ohio" district="Hamilton City School District" districtId="Hamilton City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:42:51+00:00">
    <JobTitle>VOLLEYBALL, GIRLS VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The VOLLEYBALL, GIRLS VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH at Hamilton High School - Main Campus is a comprehensive coaching role that combines instruction, mentorship, and program management. This long‑form description reflects the multifaceted nature of school coaching, where the coach is both a technical expert and a caring adult presence in the lives of student‑athletes. The position is ideal for someone who values structure, communication, and collaboration while maintaining a clear focus on student development.

Day to day, the VOLLEYBALL, GIRLS VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH plans and leads practices that prioritize safety, learning, and steady improvement. A typical session might include dynamic warm‑ups, small‑group drills, competitive games, and review conversations that help athletes understand why they are working on certain skills. The coach explains expectations clearly, uses age‑appropriate language, and adapts instruction so that athletes at different experience levels can participate and progress.

Another key element of the job is fostering positive habits. Coaches at Hamilton High School - Main Campus reinforce punctuality, preparedness, and respectful communication. The VOLLEYBALL, GIRLS VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH expects athletes to bring the proper equipment, to listen when others are speaking, and to take responsibility for their effort and behavior. When mistakes occur, the coach responds with guidance and accountability rather than embarrassment, reinforcing that learning is an ongoing process.

The role also emphasizes alignment with the school’s mission. Athletics is treated as part of the educational program, not as a separate or higher priority. That means the VOLLEYBALL, GIRLS VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH supports academic expectations, respects teachers’ roles, and encourages athletes to manage their time effectively. By checking in on grades and reinforcing eligibility requirements, the coach helps students see the connection between their everyday decisions and their opportunities to compete.

Operationally, the position involves logistics such as coordinating with transportation, ensuring facilities are left in good condition, communicating schedules, and maintaining equipment inventories. The coach understands district policies, league rules, and safety procedures, and follows them consistently. Maintaining required certifications and participating in professional development keeps the coach informed about best practices in training and athlete welfare.

In addition, the VOLLEYBALL, GIRLS VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH may contribute to long‑term program building through youth clinics, off‑season activities, and collaboration with other levels of the program. By investing in relationships with families and younger athletes, the coach helps sustain interest and continuity in the sport at Hamilton High School - Main Campus. Candidates who enjoy balancing big‑picture planning with day‑to‑day teaching will find this position engaging and fulfilling.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Hamilton High School - Main Campus</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-06-10</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>UNTIL FILLED</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/bcc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=37194&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/bcc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=37194&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/bcc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=37194&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Hamilton High School - Main Campus</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Hamilton City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Hamilton High School - Main Campus</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Volleyball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="c105c611-04b1-47f3-ac27-0ef78b0ada76" state="Ohio" district="Hamilton City School District" districtId="Hamilton City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:42:59+00:00">
    <JobTitle>WRESTLING, VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH (2)</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The WRESTLING, VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH (2) role at Hamilton High School - Main Campus is focused on building a competitive, well‑organized program that still prioritizes the overall well‑being of student‑athletes. This position blends strategy, culture‑building, and teaching, providing the coach with an opportunity to influence the direction of the program for years to come. The successful candidate will bring a clear vision for how to teach the sport, how to manage a team, and how to represent the school in a positive and professional manner.

From a competitive standpoint, the WRESTLING, VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH (2) is responsible for developing seasonal plans that align practice content, conditioning work, and game preparation. This includes designing practice segments that progress from individual fundamentals to full‑team tactical execution. The coach should be comfortable breaking down film, identifying areas for improvement, and communicating game plans in a way that athletes can understand and apply under pressure.

Equally important is the culture created by the coach. At Hamilton High School - Main Campus, teams are expected to demonstrate sportsmanship, respect, and unity. The WRESTLING, VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH (2) sets standards for effort in practice, behavior in the classroom, and conduct in the community. That might involve establishing team guidelines, leading discussions about values, and recognizing athletes who demonstrate leadership or growth in those areas. The goal is to build a program where success is measured not just by wins and losses but by the quality of the experience for everyone involved.

This position also involves close coordination with the academic side of the school. The coach monitors eligibility, encourages students to keep up with assignments, and celebrates academic milestones. Communicating with teachers and counselors when necessary helps support student‑athletes as whole people, not just as performers in one activity. At Hamilton High School - Main Campus, the WRESTLING, VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH (2) is viewed as part of the educational team.

Program administration tasks include managing equipment and uniforms, tracking inventory, assisting with scheduling, and following all district and league regulations. The coach should be organized, punctual, and attentive to details such as transportation arrangements and roster paperwork. Safety protocols, including emergency action planning and injury‑reporting procedures, must be consistently followed.

Overall, the WRESTLING, VARSITY ASSISTANT COACH (2) at Hamilton High School - Main Campus is best suited for a coach who is excited about teaching, willing to collaborate with colleagues, and prepared to invest in the growth of student‑athletes over multiple seasons. It is an opportunity to provide structure, challenge, and support while representing the school with pride in the larger athletic community.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Hamilton High School - Main Campus</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-08-26</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>UNTIL FILLED</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/bcc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=37194&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/bcc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=37194&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/bcc/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?district=37194&amp;category=Athletics%2FActivities</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Hamilton High School - Main Campus</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Hamilton City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Hamilton High School - Main Campus</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="95b7e4ac-00bf-4ea3-83b2-4d4655dd81d1" state="Ohio" district="Gahanna-Jefferson Public Schools" districtId="Gahanna-Jefferson Public Schools" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:43:09+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach (50%)</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach role at Lincoln High School is focused on helping student‑athletes unlock their potential through intentional coaching, structured practice environments, and a strong emphasis on character. This description outlines a position in which the coach is expected to be a planner, a teacher, a mentor, and a positive representative of the school community. Successful candidates bring energy to practices, patience to instruction, and clarity to expectations.

Practices form the backbone of the program, and the Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach is responsible for designing sessions that are purposeful and efficient. Each practice should have defined goals, from teaching new concepts to reinforcing previously learned skills or preparing for upcoming competition. The coach uses a variety of drills and teaching methods to keep athletes engaged, and regularly evaluates whether the team is progressing in the desired areas.

Coaches at Lincoln High School are also trusted to guide student‑athletes through challenges. That can include addressing frustrations after a tough loss, helping a student handle the pressure of increased responsibility, or supporting someone who is balancing school, family, and activities. The Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach listens, provides perspective, and reinforces the idea that effort, attitude, and resilience are as important as any statistical outcome.

Communication is a key strength of this position. The coach shares information about schedules, team policies, and expectations with families and staff in a timely and professional way. Within the team, the Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach encourages athletes to ask questions, give feedback, and support one another. This open communication helps prevent misunderstandings and builds trust.

Safety and compliance cannot be overlooked. The Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach follows all relevant policies regarding equipment, supervision, travel, and emergency procedures. The coach maintains current certifications as required and keeps up with best practices around conditioning, concussion awareness, and hydration. At Lincoln High School, the well‑being of student‑athletes is non‑negotiable.

This role is a good match for coaches who appreciate structure, care deeply about students, and are committed to building a consistent, values‑driven program. By serving as the Assistant Girls Lacrosse Coach at Lincoln High School, a coach has the opportunity to make a lasting impact on young people while contributing to a respected and sustainable athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Lincoln High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-09-08</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gahannaschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gahannaschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/gahannaschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Lincoln High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Gahanna-Jefferson Public Schools coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Lincoln High School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Lacrosse</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="8e547605-875a-46c2-99bc-a151e9c9b7f3" state="Ohio" district="Sylvania City School District" districtId="Sylvania City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:43:41+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Wrestling Coach - Junior High</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Wrestling Coach - Junior High role at McCord is focused on building a competitive, well‑organized program that still prioritizes the overall well‑being of student‑athletes. This position blends strategy, culture‑building, and teaching, providing the coach with an opportunity to influence the direction of the program for years to come. The successful candidate will bring a clear vision for how to teach the sport, how to manage a team, and how to represent the school in a positive and professional manner.

From a competitive standpoint, the Wrestling Coach - Junior High is responsible for developing seasonal plans that align practice content, conditioning work, and game preparation. This includes designing practice segments that progress from individual fundamentals to full‑team tactical execution. The coach should be comfortable breaking down film, identifying areas for improvement, and communicating game plans in a way that athletes can understand and apply under pressure.

Equally important is the culture created by the coach. At McCord, teams are expected to demonstrate sportsmanship, respect, and unity. The Wrestling Coach - Junior High sets standards for effort in practice, behavior in the classroom, and conduct in the community. That might involve establishing team guidelines, leading discussions about values, and recognizing athletes who demonstrate leadership or growth in those areas. The goal is to build a program where success is measured not just by wins and losses but by the quality of the experience for everyone involved.

This position also involves close coordination with the academic side of the school. The coach monitors eligibility, encourages students to keep up with assignments, and celebrates academic milestones. Communicating with teachers and counselors when necessary helps support student‑athletes as whole people, not just as performers in one activity. At McCord, the Wrestling Coach - Junior High is viewed as part of the educational team.

Program administration tasks include managing equipment and uniforms, tracking inventory, assisting with scheduling, and following all district and league regulations. The coach should be organized, punctual, and attentive to details such as transportation arrangements and roster paperwork. Safety protocols, including emergency action planning and injury‑reporting procedures, must be consistently followed.

Overall, the Wrestling Coach - Junior High at McCord is best suited for a coach who is excited about teaching, willing to collaborate with colleagues, and prepared to invest in the growth of student‑athletes over multiple seasons. It is an opportunity to provide structure, challenge, and support while representing the school with pride in the larger athletic community.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>McCord, 4304 McCord Road, Sylvania, OH 43560</Location>
    <City>Sylvania</City>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode>43560</ZipCode>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2 months ago</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/SylvaniaSchools/opening/135989</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/SylvaniaSchools/opening/135989</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/SylvaniaSchools?search=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>McCord</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Sylvania City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Sylvania City School District</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="116e8877-5852-4d36-a303-e184b8ca0f1c" state="Ohio" district="Mentor Exempted Village School District" districtId="Mentor Exempted Village School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:44:29+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Track - Head Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Track - Head Coach at Shore Middle School is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Track - Head Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Shore Middle School, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Track - Head Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Track - Head Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Track - Head Coach at Shore Middle School allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Shore Middle School</Location>
    <City>Mentor</City>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2022-05-12</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2022-05-26</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Shore Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Mentor Exempted Village School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Shore Middle School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Track &amp; Field</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="65b41c1e-425a-4a84-96b0-12106a16e434" state="Ohio" district="Mentor Exempted Village School District" districtId="Mentor Exempted Village School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:45:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Wrestling - Assistant Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Wrestling - Assistant Coach at Memorial Middle School is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Wrestling - Assistant Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Memorial Middle School, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Wrestling - Assistant Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Wrestling - Assistant Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Wrestling - Assistant Coach at Memorial Middle School allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Memorial Middle School</Location>
    <City>Mentor</City>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-05-15</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-05-29</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Memorial Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Mentor Exempted Village School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Memorial Middle School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="b63a4942-9609-4c53-b28e-1f2a72c70ccc" state="Ohio" district="Mentor Exempted Village School District" districtId="Mentor Exempted Village School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:47:26+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Tennis - Girls Head Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Tennis - Girls Head Coach at Mentor High School is an integral member of the school's educational team, using athletics as a platform for teaching discipline, teamwork, and perseverance. This position calls for a coach who is organized, reflective, and committed to continuous improvement, both for themselves and for their athletes. The role blends hands‑on coaching with program administration and relationship‑building.

From a coaching standpoint, the Tennis - Girls Head Coach is responsible for teaching the rules, techniques, and strategies of the sport in a way that is accessible to student‑athletes. Practices are planned to include progressive skill work, position‑specific instruction, and opportunities for athletes to apply learning in controlled scrimmage situations. The coach pays attention to pacing and variety so that sessions remain engaging while still challenging students to stretch their comfort zones.

Culture is a central focus of this job. At Mentor High School, the Tennis - Girls Head Coach helps create a team environment where respect, honesty, and effort are expected. The coach sets clear standards regarding communication, attendance, and sportsmanship, and works with athletes to understand why these standards matter. When expectations are not met, the coach responds fairly, explaining consequences and encouraging athletes to learn from mistakes.

The position also requires responsiveness to student needs. Coaches remain aware of the emotional and academic pressures students face and adjust support accordingly. Checking in with athletes, acknowledging their efforts, and partnering with school staff all contribute to a positive experience. The Tennis - Girls Head Coach may assist in connecting students with resources when additional support is needed.

Outside of direct coaching, the role involves tasks such as coordinating with officials and opponents, assisting with scheduling, and managing team communication channels. The coach must be punctual, prepared, and detail‑oriented, ensuring that events run smoothly and that the team represents Mentor High School well at home and away.

Safety remains an ongoing responsibility. The Tennis - Girls Head Coach follows district guidelines, maintains necessary certifications, and emphasizes proper warm‑up routines and technique to minimize risk of injury. This comprehensive approach to coaching allows student‑athletes to pursue their goals in a structured environment that prioritizes learning, well‑being, and long‑term success.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Mentor High School</Location>
    <City>Mentor</City>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-05-15</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-05-29</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Mentor High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Mentor Exempted Village School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Mentor High School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Tennis</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="21496e5b-b8a8-48d4-bfe3-03a0eddac7bf" state="Ohio" district="Mentor Exempted Village School District" districtId="Mentor Exempted Village School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:48:25+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Softball - Assistant Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Softball - Assistant Coach at Mentor Exempted Village School District is an integral member of the school's educational team, using athletics as a platform for teaching discipline, teamwork, and perseverance. This position calls for a coach who is organized, reflective, and committed to continuous improvement, both for themselves and for their athletes. The role blends hands‑on coaching with program administration and relationship‑building.

From a coaching standpoint, the Softball - Assistant Coach is responsible for teaching the rules, techniques, and strategies of the sport in a way that is accessible to student‑athletes. Practices are planned to include progressive skill work, position‑specific instruction, and opportunities for athletes to apply learning in controlled scrimmage situations. The coach pays attention to pacing and variety so that sessions remain engaging while still challenging students to stretch their comfort zones.

Culture is a central focus of this job. At Mentor Exempted Village School District, the Softball - Assistant Coach helps create a team environment where respect, honesty, and effort are expected. The coach sets clear standards regarding communication, attendance, and sportsmanship, and works with athletes to understand why these standards matter. When expectations are not met, the coach responds fairly, explaining consequences and encouraging athletes to learn from mistakes.

The position also requires responsiveness to student needs. Coaches remain aware of the emotional and academic pressures students face and adjust support accordingly. Checking in with athletes, acknowledging their efforts, and partnering with school staff all contribute to a positive experience. The Softball - Assistant Coach may assist in connecting students with resources when additional support is needed.

Outside of direct coaching, the role involves tasks such as coordinating with officials and opponents, assisting with scheduling, and managing team communication channels. The coach must be punctual, prepared, and detail‑oriented, ensuring that events run smoothly and that the team represents Mentor Exempted Village School District well at home and away.

Safety remains an ongoing responsibility. The Softball - Assistant Coach follows district guidelines, maintains necessary certifications, and emphasizes proper warm‑up routines and technique to minimize risk of injury. This comprehensive approach to coaching allows student‑athletes to pursue their goals in a structured environment that prioritizes learning, well‑being, and long‑term success.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>Mentor Exempted Village School District</Location>
    <City>Mentor</City>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-08-08</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-08-22</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Mentor Exempted Village School District</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Mentor Exempted Village School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Mentor Exempted Village School District</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Softball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="173a7fdb-0d9c-4c00-aa6f-3445575064c0" state="Ohio" district="Willoughby-Eastlake City School District" districtId="Willoughby-Eastlake City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:49:57+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Baseball Head Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Baseball Head Coach at W-E South High School is a comprehensive coaching role that combines instruction, mentorship, and program management. This long‑form description reflects the multifaceted nature of school coaching, where the coach is both a technical expert and a caring adult presence in the lives of student‑athletes. The position is ideal for someone who values structure, communication, and collaboration while maintaining a clear focus on student development.

Day to day, the Baseball Head Coach plans and leads practices that prioritize safety, learning, and steady improvement. A typical session might include dynamic warm‑ups, small‑group drills, competitive games, and review conversations that help athletes understand why they are working on certain skills. The coach explains expectations clearly, uses age‑appropriate language, and adapts instruction so that athletes at different experience levels can participate and progress.

Another key element of the job is fostering positive habits. Coaches at W-E South High School reinforce punctuality, preparedness, and respectful communication. The Baseball Head Coach expects athletes to bring the proper equipment, to listen when others are speaking, and to take responsibility for their effort and behavior. When mistakes occur, the coach responds with guidance and accountability rather than embarrassment, reinforcing that learning is an ongoing process.

The role also emphasizes alignment with the school’s mission. Athletics is treated as part of the educational program, not as a separate or higher priority. That means the Baseball Head Coach supports academic expectations, respects teachers’ roles, and encourages athletes to manage their time effectively. By checking in on grades and reinforcing eligibility requirements, the coach helps students see the connection between their everyday decisions and their opportunities to compete.

Operationally, the position involves logistics such as coordinating with transportation, ensuring facilities are left in good condition, communicating schedules, and maintaining equipment inventories. The coach understands district policies, league rules, and safety procedures, and follows them consistently. Maintaining required certifications and participating in professional development keeps the coach informed about best practices in training and athlete welfare.

In addition, the Baseball Head Coach may contribute to long‑term program building through youth clinics, off‑season activities, and collaboration with other levels of the program. By investing in relationships with families and younger athletes, the coach helps sustain interest and continuity in the sport at W-E South High School. Candidates who enjoy balancing big‑picture planning with day‑to‑day teaching will find this position engaging and fulfilling.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>W-E South High School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-06-16</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-06-21</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=9014</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=9014</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>W-E South High School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Willoughby-Eastlake City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>W-E South High School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Baseball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="427ba41d-9c75-4978-8f54-5e1a70bbe22f" state="Ohio" district="Willoughby-Eastlake City School District" districtId="Willoughby-Eastlake City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:50:14+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School role at W-E Willoughby Middle School is focused on helping student‑athletes unlock their potential through intentional coaching, structured practice environments, and a strong emphasis on character. This description outlines a position in which the coach is expected to be a planner, a teacher, a mentor, and a positive representative of the school community. Successful candidates bring energy to practices, patience to instruction, and clarity to expectations.

Practices form the backbone of the program, and the Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School is responsible for designing sessions that are purposeful and efficient. Each practice should have defined goals, from teaching new concepts to reinforcing previously learned skills or preparing for upcoming competition. The coach uses a variety of drills and teaching methods to keep athletes engaged, and regularly evaluates whether the team is progressing in the desired areas.

Coaches at W-E Willoughby Middle School are also trusted to guide student‑athletes through challenges. That can include addressing frustrations after a tough loss, helping a student handle the pressure of increased responsibility, or supporting someone who is balancing school, family, and activities. The Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School listens, provides perspective, and reinforces the idea that effort, attitude, and resilience are as important as any statistical outcome.

Communication is a key strength of this position. The coach shares information about schedules, team policies, and expectations with families and staff in a timely and professional way. Within the team, the Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School encourages athletes to ask questions, give feedback, and support one another. This open communication helps prevent misunderstandings and builds trust.

Safety and compliance cannot be overlooked. The Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School follows all relevant policies regarding equipment, supervision, travel, and emergency procedures. The coach maintains current certifications as required and keeps up with best practices around conditioning, concussion awareness, and hydration. At W-E Willoughby Middle School, the well‑being of student‑athletes is non‑negotiable.

This role is a good match for coaches who appreciate structure, care deeply about students, and are committed to building a consistent, values‑driven program. By serving as the Football, Assistant Coach, Middle School at W-E Willoughby Middle School, a coach has the opportunity to make a lasting impact on young people while contributing to a respected and sustainable athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Assistant Coach</JobType>
    <Location>W-E Willoughby Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-17</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-03-24</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=7739</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=7739</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>W-E Willoughby Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Willoughby-Eastlake City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>W-E Willoughby Middle School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Football</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="55b5b25d-16d5-4bd3-8f23-030784bd4cb0" state="Ohio" district="Willoughby-Eastlake City School District" districtId="Willoughby-Eastlake City School District" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:50:30+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Basketball Head Coach, 7th Grade, girls</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Basketball Head Coach, 7th Grade, girls at W-E Willoughby Middle School is a high‑engagement coaching role that calls for energy, clear communication, and a steady presence for student‑athletes. This position is built for a coach who enjoys being actively involved in every aspect of the program, from leading warm‑ups and teaching tactics to meeting with families and coordinating logistics. The coach is expected to bring consistency and enthusiasm to each interaction with the team.

Practices led by the Basketball Head Coach, 7th Grade, girls are structured and purposeful. They begin with appropriate warm‑ups, transition into focused skill work, and conclude with competitive or situational activities that resemble live play. The coach introduces concepts in manageable steps and checks for understanding, encouraging athletes to ask questions and learn the reasoning behind drills and strategies. This approach helps athletes become smarter, more confident players.

Motivation is another key component of the job. Coaches at W-E Willoughby Middle School use positive reinforcement, high yet realistic expectations, and clear feedback to help athletes push themselves. The Basketball Head Coach, 7th Grade, girls recognizes effort and improvement, not just outcomes, and supports athletes through setbacks. This creates an environment where students are willing to take risks and grow.

The role also includes a strong communication element. The coach keeps families informed about schedules, travel, and program expectations, and responds to questions in a respectful, timely manner. Within the school, the Basketball Head Coach, 7th Grade, girls collaborates with administrators and teachers to support students’ academic responsibilities, reinforcing that success in the classroom is essential.

Finally, the position requires adherence to safety and policy standards. The Basketball Head Coach, 7th Grade, girls maintains appropriate supervision ratios, follows guidelines on equipment use, and ensures that emergency procedures are understood and practiced. The coach models appropriate conduct toward officials and opponents, reinforcing that competing with integrity is a core expectation at W-E Willoughby Middle School. This comprehensive role is well suited to coaches who are organized, student‑focused, and eager to contribute to a strong athletic tradition.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType>Head Coach</JobType>
    <Location>W-E Willoughby Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-03-17</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-03-24</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=7743</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=7743</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/lcesc/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackPostingSearch=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>W-E Willoughby Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Willoughby-Eastlake City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>W-E Willoughby Middle School</CompanyName>
    <Sport>Basketball</Sport>
  </Job>
  <Job id="a6e01319-ca9c-4662-8cb7-509e1168c041" state="Ohio" district="Sylvania City School District" districtId="" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:43:41+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Wrestling Coach - Junior High</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Wrestling Coach - Junior High role at Sylvania City School District emphasizes collaboration, consistency, and long‑term program development. This position is ideal for a coach who enjoys working as part of a broader athletic staff and who values building connections across grade levels and teams. The goal is to help create a smooth pathway for student‑athletes as they progress, while maintaining a recognizable identity and standard of excellence for the program.

In practical terms, the Wrestling Coach - Junior High coordinates closely with the athletic director and fellow coaches to align terminology, teaching priorities, and expectations. This might involve participating in coaching meetings, sharing practice plans, and adapting approaches so that athletes experience similar structures and messages at each level. At Sylvania City School District, the program is strongest when coaches communicate and support one another.

Day‑to‑day responsibilities include designing practices that teach core skills, reinforcing team concepts, and preparing athletes for competition. The coach works to balance repetition with variety, ensuring that key fundamentals are constantly reinforced while athletes also experience new challenges. The Wrestling Coach - Junior High reviews performance with the team, helping athletes learn how to analyze both successes and mistakes in a constructive way.

The role extends into community and family engagement. Coaches represent Sylvania City School District at games, parent meetings, and potential youth outreach events. The Wrestling Coach - Junior High may help host clinics or camps, encourage younger students to try the sport, and provide information about expectations to families who are new to the program. A welcoming, organized presence can greatly influence how the program is perceived.

Athlete support is ongoing. The Wrestling Coach - Junior High monitors team morale, assists students in managing the demands of school and sport, and reinforces the importance of rest, nutrition, and healthy habits. The coach keeps the focus on sustainable growth rather than shortcuts, emphasizing that consistent effort over time leads to meaningful improvement.

Administrative tasks such as roster management, schedule communication, and equipment oversight are also part of the position. The Wrestling Coach - Junior High must handle these responsibilities reliably, as they are essential to maintaining a well‑run program. Coaches who enjoy seeing the big picture, who are willing to share ideas, and who care about the experience of every athlete will thrive in this role at Sylvania City School District.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>McCord, Sylvania, OH</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate/>
    <ClosingDate/>
    <JobUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/SylvaniaSchools/opening/135989</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/SylvaniaSchools/opening/135989</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://jobs.redroverk12.com/org/SylvaniaSchools?search=coach</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Sylvania City School District</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Sylvania City School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Sylvania City School District</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="042dabec-cce3-49c2-a74f-dbf3c5c27cec" state="Ohio" district="Mentor Exempted Village School District" districtId="" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:45:48+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Wrestling - Assistant Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Wrestling - Assistant Coach role at Memorial Middle School emphasizes collaboration, consistency, and long‑term program development. This position is ideal for a coach who enjoys working as part of a broader athletic staff and who values building connections across grade levels and teams. The goal is to help create a smooth pathway for student‑athletes as they progress, while maintaining a recognizable identity and standard of excellence for the program.

In practical terms, the Wrestling - Assistant Coach coordinates closely with the athletic director and fellow coaches to align terminology, teaching priorities, and expectations. This might involve participating in coaching meetings, sharing practice plans, and adapting approaches so that athletes experience similar structures and messages at each level. At Memorial Middle School, the program is strongest when coaches communicate and support one another.

Day‑to‑day responsibilities include designing practices that teach core skills, reinforcing team concepts, and preparing athletes for competition. The coach works to balance repetition with variety, ensuring that key fundamentals are constantly reinforced while athletes also experience new challenges. The Wrestling - Assistant Coach reviews performance with the team, helping athletes learn how to analyze both successes and mistakes in a constructive way.

The role extends into community and family engagement. Coaches represent Memorial Middle School at games, parent meetings, and potential youth outreach events. The Wrestling - Assistant Coach may help host clinics or camps, encourage younger students to try the sport, and provide information about expectations to families who are new to the program. A welcoming, organized presence can greatly influence how the program is perceived.

Athlete support is ongoing. The Wrestling - Assistant Coach monitors team morale, assists students in managing the demands of school and sport, and reinforces the importance of rest, nutrition, and healthy habits. The coach keeps the focus on sustainable growth rather than shortcuts, emphasizing that consistent effort over time leads to meaningful improvement.

Administrative tasks such as roster management, schedule communication, and equipment oversight are also part of the position. The Wrestling - Assistant Coach must handle these responsibilities reliably, as they are essential to maintaining a well‑run program. Coaches who enjoy seeing the big picture, who are willing to share ideas, and who care about the experience of every athlete will thrive in this role at Memorial Middle School.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Wrestling</Sport>
    <Location>Memorial Middle School</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-05-15</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-05-29</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5005</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5005</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Memorial Middle School</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Mentor Exempted Village School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Memorial Middle School</CompanyName>
  </Job>
  <Job id="07c85589-0117-4db2-9cc9-001802e0bf02" state="Ohio" district="Mentor Exempted Village School District" districtId="" active="true" lastSeen="2025-12-02T06:48:25+00:00">
    <JobTitle>Softball - Assistant Coach</JobTitle>
    <JobDescription>
The Softball - Assistant Coach at Mentor Exempted Village School District is a comprehensive coaching assignment where teaching, organization, and care for students come together in a single role. The coach is expected to be prepared, professional, and consistent, creating a framework in which athletes understand what is expected of them and feel supported in meeting those expectations. The program thrives when the coach brings a balanced focus on performance, safety, and personal development.

During practices, the Softball - Assistant Coach manages time efficiently, moving athletes through warm‑ups, skill stations, team concepts, and competitive play. The coach provides instruction and feedback that is specific and actionable, helping athletes understand not just what to do, but why it matters. Attention is given to fundamentals, conditioning appropriate to the sport and season, and mental preparation for competition.

The position carries a strong responsibility for modeling behavior. At Mentor Exempted Village School District, coaches are role models whether they are on the sideline, traveling with the team, or speaking with families. The Softball - Assistant Coach demonstrates composure, fairness, and respect, even in emotionally charged situations. Athletes observe and imitate these behaviors, so the coach’s example has a direct impact on team culture.

The role also involves building strong connections with the broader school community. The coach collaborates with staff members, responds to communication from parents and guardians, and participates in department or school events as appropriate. Being visible and approachable helps families feel confident that their children are in a safe, supportive program.

Safety and compliance requirements form an important foundation. The Softball - Assistant Coach follows all district and league regulations, maintains necessary certifications, and ensures that facilities and equipment are used appropriately. Emergency procedures are understood and practiced so that the team is prepared if an unexpected situation occurs.

This position is well suited to coaches who are detail‑oriented, who enjoy planning and facilitating engaging practices, and who care about the long‑term lessons students take away from their time in athletics. Serving as the Softball - Assistant Coach at Mentor Exempted Village School District allows a coach to influence not only competitive outcomes, but also the habits and character of the next generation.
    </JobDescription>
    <JobType/>
    <Sport>Softball</Sport>
    <Location>Mentor, OH</Location>
    <City/>
    <State>OH</State>
    <Country/>
    <ZipCode/>
    <Experience/>
    <SalaryRange/>
    <Benefits/>
    <PostingDate>2025-08-08</PostingDate>
    <ClosingDate>2025-08-22</ClosingDate>
    <JobUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5122</JobUrl>
    <ApplyUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/default.aspx?AppliTrackJobId=5122</ApplyUrl>
    <CoachSearchUrl>https://www.applitrack.com/mentorschools/onlineapp/jobpostings/view.asp?category=Athletics%2FActivities&amp;subcategory=Coaching</CoachSearchUrl>
    <EmployerEmail/>
    <EmployerFullName>Mentor Exempted Village School District</EmployerFullName>
    <CompanyDescription>Mentor Exempted Village School District coaching jobs</CompanyDescription>
    <CompanyEmail/>
    <CompanyName>Mentor Exempted Village School District</CompanyName>
  </Job>
</Jobs>
